BUSINESS PROPOSAL
EPISODE 9
You won't say
this is a mistake too, right?
I'll pay you back for that kiss
with another kiss.
What's going on here?
First of all,
I'm very sorry.
-What?
-As you probably know,
I'm not President Kang.
I'm Cha Sung-hoon, his secretary.
-What?
-President Kang
has someone else
that he wishes to marry.
I'm here instead, since this meeting
couldn't go on as planned.
I'm very sorry.
Hello?
Hey, you're up. Did you sleep well?
Yes. How about you?
I didn't sleep well.
Why?
Because I missed you so much.
Come on, what are you saying?
I'm in front of your house.
Let's go on a date before work.
What?
But it'll take a while
for me to get ready.
It's okay. I'll wait. Take your time.
Although…
I want to see you as soon as possible.
What?
Does he want me to take my time
or hurry up? What should I do?
Are you okay?
Should I go get some medicine?
No, it's fine.
I'll be fine after eating some soup.
-It's hot!
-Here.
Just how much did you drink yesterday?
My team members are heavy drinkers.
By the way, this soup is so good.
You're a good cook.
These are all my company's products,
and I'm a terrible cook.
Mr. Kang is a good cook.
Right. I heard that Kang Tae-moo
went on a blind date with Yu-jeong.
How could he do that when he has Ha-ri?
What's wrong with him?
Young-seo, actually--
I have a morning meeting!
I'm so forgetful.
I have to run, Sung-hoon.
Thank you so much for the food.
I hope your business trip goes well.
I'll text you.
Text me!
This place is really popular nowadays.
I didn't know they were open at this hour.
My friend owns this place.
He did me a favor.
Please, sit.
Thank you.
I'm going on a business trip to the States
so I wanted to have breakfast together.
Wait here.
You're going to cook yourself?
Yes. The most popular
brunch course here was my idea.
I'll make you the original version,
so just you wait.
I'm already worried
that you'll love it and ask me
to make it for you every day.
Thank you for the meal.
Why aren't you eating?
This is so pretty. Can I take a picture?
What about me?
I'm the one who did all the work.
Sorry.
Why, this…
Your shoes…
What about my shoes?
You missed me so much that you didn't
know you put on mismatched shoes?
Wait…
Why did I…
Wait, your earrings are…
They're two different earrings?
No, they're pretty.
Darn it.
Are you having fun teasing me?
Yes.
Fine.
I was so nervous
that I put on two different shoes.
And I don't even know
if I can digest this food.
I don't usually get this nervous.
Why am I being so nervous?
I look so stupid, don't I?
You keep cheating.
What do you mean, cheating?
My heart just skipped a beat
because you're so cute.
What are you doing?
My face is getting a bit red
right now, right?
Can you not look at me? I'm embarrassed.
We'll be right on time if we leave now.
No, let's go separately from here.
Why? Let me drive you somewhere near work.
What if someone sees me
getting out of your car?
But it's a pretty long way.
It's okay, I'll take the bus.
Drive safely.
You know, this was
the most wonderful morning of my life.
-Ms. Kim. Good morning.
-Hello.
Good morning.
Hello.
How come you're coming in together?
We met in front of the building.
Yes, in front. In the morning.
You know, I smelled grapefruit
when you three came in.
It's not me.
It's coming from Ms. Yeo.
Mr. Gye smells like it too.
You two must use the same shampoo.
Come on. I don't like that.
Why do you use the same shampoo as me?
That's what I should say.
I should wash my hair again. Really.
What's wrong with that?
You guys are overreacting.
Right?
Right! Congratulations, Ms. Shin.
-On what?
-What do you think?
Because of that video, Ms. Shin…
The video's a huge hit.
-A huge hit?
-Yes.
Because Ms. Shin mentioned
that we don't use any artificial coloring,
our sales have increased by 20 percent.
Really?
Did you
have a good time with Ms. Shin yesterday?
I'm not telling you.
You didn't tell me who you were dating.
I'll get going, then.
Oh, right. Get me some women's heels.
The size
should be 230.
What? Why do you need women's heels
all of a sudden?
Who are they for?
My girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
No way.
Is Ms. Shin Ha-ri here?
That's me.
What is it?
Your boyfriend sent you a gift.
Boyfriend?
Could you sign here?
What is it?
Ms. Shin, are you dating someone
in secret?
What's the gift? Let me see.
Let's see.
What? They're heels.
Right! You've been upset today
because you wore mismatched shoes.
What? Then did your boyfriend
send these knowing about that?
I think Young-seo sent these.
I sent her a text about it earlier,
so she must have decided
to play a joke on me.
Right. You mean
the daughter of Marine Group?
-Yes.
-Right? You had me going there.
That makes sense.
These are really expensive.
She really is rich.
The data shows
that the white kimchi ravioli
developed by Researcher Shin Ha-ri
and Chef Lee Min-woo
had the highest sales rate.
Also, our future sales will
be positively impacted
by Ms. Shin's comment on our video…
If it wasn't for this trip,
I'd go on a date with Ms. Shin.
Should I delay the trip?
I shouldn't, right?
This is driving me nuts.
President Kang, is there
something wrong with the report?
HA-RI! MS. SHIN
It's nothing. Please continue.
What's the occasion? You usually
only wear slippers while working.
Well, no reason.
I'm so tired.
Developing a new product
and renewing our existing products?
Why is this company
giving us so much work?
Thank you for your hard work.
Goodness.
You don't have to mention it, sir.
This company is like my family,
and to work hard for it
is my joy and happiness.
-To what do we owe the pleasure?
-I have something to say
to Ms. Shin.
To me?
What is it that you want to…
I heard you've been busy lately
because of the video shoot.
Yes.
So I made some adjustments
to your schedule.
About the Bucket List Fish.
HA-RI! MS. SHIN
About the plan, I--
Sir, are you all right?
Ms. Shin, why did you do that?
Why is there a fly here?
-A fly?
-What do you mean, a fly?
It's thoroughly sanitized here.
No, I saw it too. A fly. There.
You'll be late for your flight.
Wait, I'll send you the schedule
by email via Team Leader Lee.
A fly?
-Where is the fly?
-That's weird.
There's no way a fly is in here.
By the way, isn't President Kang
acting weird today?
He kept smiling at Ms. Shin
as he was talking.
Naturally.
The sales have gone up thanks to Ms. Shin.
I bet he's really thankful.
True.
That's true.
Right?
I bet he just can't help
but smile when he sees me.
What?
Is she showing off now that he favors her?
Yes.
She says yes.
It's a pleasure to work with you
The pleasure is mine. Thank you.
-Thank you.
Right now, the time in Seoul…
It should be around eight.
She must've gotten off work, right?
I really don't know anymore.
I think that it'll be best if you decide.
PRESIDENT KANG
So I've been thinking, Ms. Shin.
Ms. Shin, you know that there's
no toilet paper in the bathroom, right?
What's the matter?
You surprised me.
No, go ahead and smoke.
Why is it so hard…
To take one call?
Why isn't she picking up now?
If things didn't work out with Yu-jeong,
then we need to
schedule your next blind date!
But you ran off
and went on a business trip!
He's yelling at me
to go on a blind date again.
Should I just tell him
that I'm seeing Ms. Shin?
Then…
you'll have to tell him
Shin Geum-hui is Shin Ha-ri
and explain everything that's happened.
Will it be okay?
Mr. Cha, are you busy?
Why aren't you checking my texts?
Please text me back.
Please?
I thought I ended things that day,
so why is she doing this?
President Kang has someone else
that he wishes to marry.
I'm very sorry.
Oh, my god.
This is destiny.
It's fate.
What?
What are you--
You're totally my type.
Do you want to date me?
That…
won't be possible.
Why? Am I not your type?
Or are you married?
It's not like that.
I have a girlfriend.
Who cares?
You're not even married,
so it doesn't matter.
Let's just give it a try.
I'll give up
if you don't change your mind.
Okay?
I don't think I can.
I'm very sorry.
Come on.
Yes, Ms. Jin.
You must be busy because of work, right?
Still, don't skip any meals, okay?
Why is he ignoring my text?
Is he really busy?
Yes, okay. I'll call you later.
You're not wearing
anything that's the same as me today!
YOU HAVE A NEW MESSAGE
I'm on a business trip.
I'll contact you when I'm back,
so stop texting me.
Don't skip your meals too, Young-seo.
He'll contact me when he's back.
Thank goodness.
Did something good happen?
You look so happy.
I could say the same thing.
It seems like you have something
that makes you so happy.
Haven't I told you?
I'm…
seeing someone.
Really?
Oh, my! I am too!
Ms. Han, Mr. Shin.
Congratulations on being discharged
from the hospital.
There's no need to bow.
I'm sorry I didn't visit
you two at the hospital.
We know that it's because you were busy.
-Mom, did we have guests?
-Yes.
The people from your dad's hiking club
and my friends.
Oh, right. Ha-ri.
People asked me
to get them your autograph.
Dong-cheol's son became your fan
after watching the YouTube video.
That's ridiculous.
What? It's not that weird.
You're even doing an interview tomorrow.
With Min-woo.
An interview?
My daughter is pretty impressive!
I'm not.
My company's marketing team arranged it.
It's a small online article.
By the way,
why hasn't Min-woo been around?
Is he really busy?
I think so.
What? What am I doing? It's time.
It's time.
Gosh, I thought he was in pain.
That's how he is.
Do you watch this, Dad?
What?
You watch this show, too?
I heard it's nuts.
He watched every episode in the hospital
and now he's crazy about it.
He likes it more than I do.
BE STRONG, GEUM-HUI
Hey, Ha-ri.
That's the cafe
that your company launched, right?
They're so openly advertising it.
And what kind of rich person
goes to a franchise coffee shop
and picks up his own coffee?
Does that make any sense, Young-seo?
Rich people are human too.
Just look at Young-seo.
She eats tteokbokki
and fried chicken like us.
Is that so?
Well, Young-seo's an exception.
Come on, I'm trying
to watch the show here.
All right.
Chairman Kang goes to roadside
steamed bun places too.
You got some red beans on your teeth.
My teeth? Oh, my!
I saw that scene yesterday too.
So what did you want to tell me?
I see that President Kang
hasn't told you, either.
Kids these days.
Apparently…
the two of them
are seeing each other.
What?
Are you sure?
Yes, absolutely.
Yu-jeong said
that she's very busy
dating someone lately.
Wait, then is she really seeing Tae-moo?
I'm sure of it.
So I was thinking,
before people start talking about it,
what do you think
about getting those two married?
What?
Hey. It's been a while.
Yes, it has.
Ha-ri, I'm sorry about that day.
I overstepped my boundaries
because I was so worried about you.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
I thought about it and I overreacted, too.
And you must have been surprised too.
What did you and President Kang
decide to do?
We're…
seeing each other.
Really?
Of course, like you said, the two of us
might not work out.
But I decided to give it a try.
Onto the next question.
Ms. Shin, you're famous for
the "Is President Kang Watching?" meme.
Did President Kang really see it?
Yes, he did.
Then did he give you a bonus?
-No.
-He didn't?
-No, he didn't.
-He's so cheap.
I can't believe it.
Ms. Shin, on a side note,
is President Kang really that handsome?
I've only seen him in pictures.
Well, I'm not so sure.
You keep asking questions
that are hard to answer.
President Kang.
Hello, President Kang Tae-moo.
I'm Hwang Bo-ra, a reporter for Estien.
It's nice to meet you.
Here.
It's been a while, you two.
Since you're here,
could you say a few words--
I'm sorry, but I don't think so.
I think a question or two will be fine.
This question is similar to the one
I just asked Ms. Shin.
Are you going to give Ms. Shin a bonus?
Of course.
I need to keep my promise as a president.
And, Ms. Shin,
-do you want to have dinner with me today?
-What?
What? Dinner with Ms. Shin?
What's going on?
At our last company field day,
Ms. Shin was chosen as the MVP
-and won a chance to eat dinner with me.
-Right.
So let's have that dinner today.
Do you have the time?
Yes, I do.
Where are you meeting him?
At a restaurant, I'm sure.
But which restaurant?
Probably a really fancy one, right?
Well, I don't know either.
The place doesn't matter.
Just imagine eating dinner
with a guy like President Kang.
It would feel like a date.
A date, my foot.
I bet you'll feel really uncomfortable.
I was going to come get you. Get in.
Yes. Right…
The doors are closing.
Why? Wait, get in.
I'm in front of my place.
I'm almost there, too.
Why don't we have dinner together?
Sure.
I'll be waiting, then.
Okay.
Long time, no see, Mr. Cha.
Ms. Cho, what are you doing here?
In this Information Age,
you can find out anything
you put your mind to.
Mr. Cha.
Why won't you like me back?
As I told you before,
I'm not interested in you.
I simply can't give up on you!
Please.
Please reciprocate my feelings! Please?
Are you feeling okay?
Sung-hoon, it's me.
Open the door.
You're here.
I thought you'd want a home-cooked meal,
so I bought groceries.
My house is a bit dirty to cook in,
so let's cook at your place.
I don't think that's a good idea.
Why? Your house is a lot better
than mine. It's okay.
What's that noise?
President Kang is here.
Mr. Kang Tae-moo?
It's Kang Tae-moo again?
I'll call you as soon as I can
after I take care of him.
Just go wait at home, okay?
-Okay, call me.
-Sure.
Yes. I'll call you as soon as I can.
In any case,
I really don't like Kang Tae-moo.
TTEOKBOKKI, FRIES, SUNDAE, FISH CAKES
MATNA SNACK BAR
Is this really the place
you wanted to go to with me?
Yes.
What are you doing? Let's go.
I can't believe her.
A date in a place like this?
This isn't a date.
This is a dinner with President Kang.
It's an excuse for a date.
Honestly, it felt good to say it
in front of other people
after hiding it for so long.
Do you know how surprised I was
because of that?
All of the employees came out to watch.
I was just happy to see you
after such a long time.
Are you really so unhappy about it?
I mean,
I'm just saying
that we should be careful at work.
Is that why you treated
your boyfriend's call like some spam call?
That's not it.
Then what should I do?
Should I go around telling people
I'm dating the president of my company?
You're here. It's been a while.
Hi, ma'am, have you been well?
Of course.
By the way, who's this?
I've never seen him before.
He's my company's…
He's my boyfriend.
What?
When did you get
such a handsome boyfriend?
Okay.
I'll give you two some sundae,
free of charge.
You don't have to.
Thank you.
Ma'am.
Why is she the only one
getting free sundae?
We want some, too.
Yes, give us some.
-We want some, too.
-We want sundae.
-We want some too.
Students, listen!
Since the owner is giving us sundae,
I'll pay for all of your food.
How does that sound?
-Great!
I'll contact you tomorrow then.
Sorry. I keep getting work calls.
Why are you laughing like that?
The more I think about it,
the funnier it is.
I've never seen someone pay
for everyone's food at a snack bar.
It's my first time spending
that much money at a snack bar too.
Did you eat that much
when you were in high school too?
I'm not sure.
Anyway, it felt good
when you introduced me
as your boyfriend to the owner.
Do you think that I always want
to hide it from other people?
"President Kang is my boyfriend."
I want to say that confidently.
What? Why are you looking at me like that?
There's something I've been wanting to do.
Can I?
What?
You had some sauce on your cheek,
so I was going to wipe it for you.
Why did you close your eyes?
My eyes were stinging.
Why isn't he saying anything to me
when he's seeing Yu-jeong?
-Why are you staring at me?
-What?
No. It's nothing.
Is it because he's embarrassed
it hasn't been that long
since he broke up with Geum-hui?
Should I just pretend not to know
for the time being?
Oh, my God.
You scared me.
What do you want?
Can I
vent to you for a moment?
I don't think we're close enough
to listen to each other's stories.
It's because
I don't have anyone to talk to!
You know I have no friends!
Okay.
Seriously.
What's wrong?
You know the guy
that I told you about before?
It's over!
What? It hasn't even been that long. Why?
Last night, I went to his place all drunk,
and I made a huge scene!
You go wild when you're drunk.
Why did you do that?
Because…
he kept trying to draw lines with me.
-Draw lines?
-I'm saying this only to you,
but that guy is not on our level.
He's just a normal guy.
It's the first time
I've fallen for someone
without caring
about his family, assets, or background.
But now…
the end.
It's game over!
So, you're just going to give up?
What?
Where's the Yu-jeong that I know?
You're the kind of person
who never gives up and tries
until they like you back. Right?
Right.
Actually, I had to be really persistent
to get with my current boyfriend
because he kept trying
to keep his distance.
Are you kidding? Really?
It's true.
Oh, my god.
So you should go and apologize to him
and try to make it work.
You got this. You can do it, girl!
I can do it!
You got this!
Yes, you can do it.
I'm sorry I'm late.
There were so many customers.
It seemed busier than usual today.
Maybe it's because of that news article.
-Did you read it?
-Of course.
You looked great in the photo.
A lot of comments say
you two look so good together.
You know how people are.
Right.
By the way,
do you have time this weekend?
This weekend? Why?
My parents want to see you.
I think they're worried since we keep
breaking up and getting back together.
And I also think
it's about time we got married.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Let's put off meeting with your parents.
I'm so busy with work these days,
and I don't think…
I'm ready for that yet.
Did something happen yesterday?
What? Why?
You look upset, so I was wondering
if you fought with Young-seo.
Actually, I have something to…
What?
What is it?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
What?
Mr. Cha.
Who…
Hello.
I'm Jo Yu-jeong. The one you were supposed
to go on a blind date with.
What brings you here?
Okay.
Actually…
I fell in love at first sight with
Mr. Cha, who showed up to the blind date
instead of you.
But Mr. Cha wouldn't
reciprocate my feelings,
so I went to his place last night
after getting drunk.
-Please, don't.
-Don't be so startled.
I thought about it,
and it was such a big mistake.
So I'm here to apologize.
What is she talking about?
Mr. Kang.
Grandfather.
So, this is Ms. Jo Yu-jeong.
And you went on that blind date
instead of Tae-moo?
That's--
I think I came at a bad time again.
What?
You little brat.
-Come here!
-Grandpa!
-You!
-Sir!
-Grandfather, calm down.
-Sir, I'm Sung-hoon!
-You went instead of him? You brat!
-It's me, Sung-hoon.
Tae-moo, you really…
Then…
who's the woman
you've been seeing?
What?
What woman?
Do you think that I don't know?
I've heard you calling her every night.
If it's not Ms. Jo,
then who's the person you've been seeing?
-That's--
-Wait.
Are you seeing Geum-hui again?
Why aren't you saying anything?
My stomach. What's wrong with it?
Are you not feeling well, sir?
Of course, I'm not feeling well!
Because of this brat!
It must be because you keep
drinking cold drinks for the menu renewal.
You be quiet!
Tae-moo.
I need to use the bathroom.
Stop the elevator on any floor.
FOOD PRODUCT DEVELOPMENT TEAM 1
Ms. Yeo, here's the data
that you asked for.
Okay.
Ms. Shin's proposal was chosen
for our newest product!
Yes.
Mr. Gye. Your proposal was good,
but it's too similar to a product
that another company sold
about three years ago.
So I excluded it
because I didn't want people saying
that we copied it.
So don't be too sad.
Right. Nowadays, people are so quick
to criticize if anything seems wrong.
So we need to be careful.
Copy? Whatever…
Of course.
I'm sure that you made the best decision.
YOU HAVE A NEW MESSAGE
Mr. Gye, what's this?
What?
You're being harsh, babe.
Do you think I copied it?
You made me look bad in front of Ms. Kim.
You sent this in the group chat?
Don't tell me you two are…
No, this is…
I was going to say something else,
but I made a typo and typed "babe."
I don't know anymore!
Babe!
I mean, "hey."
Mr. Gye!
What's wrong with Mr. Gye?
What's he talking about?
Mr. Gye.
We need to talk!
I have nothing to say to you.
Let go!
It hurts!
How am I supposed to come to work now?
Mr. Gye!
Wait, Ms. Yeo…
Ms. Yeo, that's the men's bathroom.
Come on.
Calm down. Let's talk.
-I don't want to talk with you!
-Come on!
I want to be alone!
Ms. Yeo!
What if someone sees you?
I mean, seriously…
-Ms. Yeo, are you all right?
-She's too strong!
-Are you okay?
-That jerk!
Are you two…
Damn it.
Sir, this way.
I can see, too.
-Don't get in the way. Move.
-Chairman Kang?
Wait,
why is there a women's shoe
in the men's bathroom?
You're right. Why is this here?
Wait a minute.
What if there's a woman in here?
Hey, who's in there?
Say something.
What?
I was right.
But why is a woman in the men's bathroom?
She must be in here by mistake.
If you do this,
she'll be too embarrassed to come out.
You should go to another bathroom.
No!
The person who shouldn't be in here
should leave. Why should I?
Listen. Come on out
before it gets even more embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
Look.
How did you end up in the men's…
Wait, Shin Ha-ri?
You're the employee who shoved me
at the bathroom last time, right?
I'm sorry.
Why are you in the men's bathroom?
Okay, just get out.
Quickly!
I'm sorry.
Jeez.
LETTER OF APOLOGY
NAME: SHIN HA-RI
Why did Chairman Kang
have to go into that bathroom?
Right. You're so unlucky.
Ms. Shin's in trouble because of you two.
So how long have you been dating?
Babe, you should tell…
You should tell them, Ms. Yeo.
Well…
On the day of the field day,
he and I went for drinks
after it was over.
Damn blind date.
Fine, I'll go.
I'm hanging up.
It's so stressful.
Didn't you say
you can't eat chicken gizzards?
You always gave them to me.
What are you doing?
You're going on a blind date?
Then I won't yield to you anymore.
What?
What do chicken gizzards
have to do with that?
Do you really think I can't eat them?
I like chicken gizzards,
and I like spicy marinated crabs, too.
But since you like them,
I pretended not to eat them
and gave them to you.
What?
But you didn't know any of that,
and now you're going on a blind date.
I think you're really drunk.
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
Hey, Yeo Ui-joo,
I'm not drunk,
so listen closely.
Don't go…
on that blind date.
Stop!
It's fine. You can stop there.
Whatever.
Hey, Ms. Shin.
Could you just write that you went into
the men's bathroom accidentally?
I was going to do that anyway.
Thanks, Ms. Shin.
I'll buy you beef today.
Prime beef.
He must hate me now.
Today, I…
Today, I accidentally made
the mistake of going into
the men's bathroom
because I was looking at my phone.
I will deeply repent for causing
Chairman Kang great mental distress
and am submitting
this letter of apology as a promise
that I will never
walk around looking at my phone again.
Are you happy now that
you've gotten that letter of apology?
So why did you just let her go?
I was going to give her
a really good scolding.
It seemed like a simple mistake.
You should just let it go, sir.
A mistake or not,
I hate that I keep getting
mixed up with her.
I don't like it!
I told you we should have a team dinner.
Why are you leaving?
I'm good.
I don't feel like drinking today.
Since when did you need
to feel like drinking to drink?
-Let's go, Ms. Shin.
-Yes.
Don't be like this.
Let's go to So's. I think that's the best.
Yes.
Let's chew on some beef,
and the chairman too.
I can't believe he made
you write a letter of apology.
Yes, chew everything up!
Let's all go to So's!
Hello, President Kang.
Are you all going somewhere?
Yes.
-The enoki mushrooms are burning.
-What?
Here.
My mistake.
I've never even imagined
that our busy president
would come to a barbeque place with us
and grill meat like this.
Please leave. Everyone is uncomfortable
because of you.
Am I making you uncomfortable?
Not at all. Why would we be uncomfortable?
She's right! I couldn't be
more comfortable than this.
-Wait…
-Take off the cover.
Mr. Kang, I have a suggestion.
What is it?
I think that we're all feeling
a bit awkward
because this is our first team dinner
with you.
How about we each have a bomb shot?
-What?
-Come on, Ms. Kim.
Having bomb shots with the president?
Don't be so embarrassing.
I like bomb shots.
-Open it!
-Okay.
-Swirl it.
-Open it?
Yes.
What?
A WORKER'S GUIDE TO LIFE
1. HOW TO MIX BOMB SHOTS
The name of this drink that I made
with my blood, sweat, and tears
is…
The Dynamite Drink!
Here!
Go ahead and try one!
-Drink!
I'll arrive in about ten minutes.
Oh, my God.
I'll see you later.
What do you want now?
It's your fault!
What's my fault?
I went to see him at work
to sincerely apologize
because you told me to.
But now I'm screwed!
Are you feeling nervous?
Yes. I'm introducing my girlfriend
to you for the first time after all.
Come on.
You're making me all nervous too.
I'm going to the bathroom for a moment.
Sure, go ahead.
Sorry, you must've been waiting long.
Something came up on my way out.
It's all right.
-About today--
-I came
with someone.
Who?
She got rejected by a guy,
so she was bawling.
And I couldn't just ignore her.
I'm so sorry.
I really didn't want to be alone today,
so I followed her
even though I know it's rude…
What? Why?
Mr. Cha is your boyfriend?
Wait a second,
the guy that you like…
I had no idea.
Then you should have told me
in the beginning!
I clearly told you I had a girlfriend!
Young-seo!
My goodness.
What's going on here?
-Mother, just a second.
-What?
Young-seo.
Young-seo!
Don't just leave like this.
Please let me explain.
Yesterday…
when you said Kang Tae-moo was
at your place, was that Yu-jeong?
Well, it was…
Yes, but let me explain.
I went on a blind date
instead of Mr. Kang--
Yu-jeong fell for you
and started bothering you,
and things ended up like this. Right?
-Yes, that's right.
-What do you mean, that's right?
What?
You shouldn't have
gone on that blind date.
You shouldn't have let Yu-jeong
into your house.
No, you should have told me the truth
from the very beginning.
I'm really sorry about everything.
It's all my fault.
I didn't imagine things would--
Do you know what's most infuriating?
It's how you ignored me
and blindly did as Kang Tae-moo said.
Are you that family's servant?
Young-seo…
Are you okay?
You seemed to be drinking a lot.
I wasn't. I drank
way less than I usually do.
Really?
Then, if you drink
more than you usually do…
what happens?
Seriously.
By the way…
about your grandfather…
Is he really not angry anymore?
He's still mad, right?
I knew it.
Don't worry about it too much.
He'll get over it.
How can I not worry about it?
He's your grandfather.
I want to be loved by the person
you love the most too.
Do you know you looked
really pretty when you said that?
Okay!
The others must be waiting.
Should we go back?
I sprayed too much.
I'm sorry.
Is Ms. Kim spinning?
-Really?
-Or are my eyes spinning?
Ms. Yeo.
Why are you drinking so little?
Let's go get another round of drinks.
We should go do karaoke next.
How's that?
I…
-President Kang, you're going too, right?
-Sure.
I'll pay for this
and for the second round too.
-President Kang!
Three beats per measure. Let's go.
President Kang.
Three beats per measure.
Okay, empty your glasses.
What are you two doing holding hands?
Who's holding whose hand?
President Kang
and Ms. Shin.
They were just holding hands.
Look.
They're not holding hands anymore.
You're drunk.
Why would President Kang
and Ms. Shin be holding hands?
It's not like they're dating.
Right.
Ms. Yeo and Mr. Gye are the ones dating.
Are the two of you
in a relationship?
Yes.
It's been a while.
It's time you went home.
You're spewing nonsense.
Yes.
No, I'm sure that those two
were holding hands.
I'm right!
-Let's go.
-Go home!
Let's go home!
I swear I saw it.
I really saw it.
I'm serious!
Why are you being so insufferable today?
I'm sorry, sir.
It's all right.
She's drunk after all.
Should I call a taxi, then?
No. There's a lot over there.
Get home safe, President Kang.
We'll take care of this bomb…
I mean, send Ms. Kim home first.
Good night, then.
What about you, Ms. Shin?
What?
You're going in
the opposite direction, right? Bye, then.
Right. Yes.
Get home safe. Right.
Everyone is in a relationship except me!
Damn this world!
Shut it!
Her specialty is public speaking, you see.
-She has a good voice.
-Right.
What?
What is he doing there?
Do you want to go for a walk to sober up?
Sure.
What are you doing there?
Subtitle translation by: Su-in Choi
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs