BUSINESS PROPOSAL
EPISODE 2
Damn it, this is what I was worried about!
I can't run into him looking like this!
What are you doing?
I…
So…
I have something I need to tell you.
-What is it?
-It's…
I just need a moment…
Before, you said that you never
wanted to see my face or marry me.
So what are you doing right now?
Exactly.
Right. Not only do I not want
to see your face ever again
but I'm also not interested
in marrying you at all.
So I came back to tell you to never
contact me again. Okay, I'll be going now.
I'm still going to marry you.
What?
So tell me why you don't want to marry me.
I don't like everything about you.
I don't like how cheesy
your weird lines are
and how your face
looks like an archaeopteryx.
An archaeopteryx?
I'll be leaving now.
Oh, it's a green light.
An archaeopteryx?
What does that look like?
This is an archaeopteryx.
How do I look anything like this?
Just the overall vibe,
especially the nose.
What?
The resemblance is uncanny.
What? How can you laugh
in a situation like this?
No, I mean, the whole thing is hilarious.
So you're telling me,
you jumped in the car and said,
"I don't want to marry you."
I had no choice. I couldn't
run into Min-woo looking like that.
Anyway, what do we do now?
He'll push ahead with the wedding
if we don't do something about it.
You're right.
Why does he even want
to get married so badly?
I told you,
he's probably after your family
so his family can become the wealthiest.
Even if the two companies merge,
that's still not enough capital, though.
Maybe he's actually just fallen for you.
That's impossible.
He's probably interested in
"Jin Young-seo from Marine Group."
Anyway, go meet him
and clear this whole thing up.
Fine.
I'm tired. Let's get going.
Come on. Let's go
for just one more round of drinks.
-What?
-If my dad comes back and finds out
that I made a complete mess
of the blind date, I'm dead.
Just one more drink. Think of it
as my last meal before I die, okay?
Fine. Let's go for another round.
Let's go!
Young-seo.
Hey, Ha-ri.
What are you doing?
Remember that guy
I told you about last time?
That's where we met.
What?
He was so my type.
I think he works somewhere around here.
Let's wait a bit, please?
Wow, that guy's the reason you decided
to come here in the first place, isn't it?
You're right.
I mean, I've never felt so right
about anything else in my life.
So let's just wait for one more hour.
How's that sound?
Fine. Okay.
Just one hour! I'll pick up the tab here.
Wow, can you believe these girls?
After coming home drunk last night,
they drank even more.
Why I ought to…
Wake up!
-Don't you have to go to work?
-My head hurts.
Mrs. Han.
Why did I fall asleep here?
-What are you doing here?
-I don't know.
Do you not remember
what happened yesterday?
Yesterday?
Look at this girl. Your sister's
not picking up her phone again.
This little brat. She's dead meat.
Ta-da!
I come bearing gifts.
This one's for Dad, Mom, and Ha-min.
And this one's for me!
Look at you. Did you get into a fight?
Oh, right. Mom, I tripped over there.
Would you look at yourself right now?
But these really nice police officers
drove us here, like this!
You got wasted and what? The police?
I can't believe you!
Just get inside!
She's here too!
Gosh, how much do you have to drink
to not be able to walk like this?
Good evening.
-Wow.
-Miss.
All right, miss. You're home now, okay?
No, I wasn't asking you
to help me find my house.
I was asking you to help me
find the man I'm destined to be with.
Hold on.
I've been telling you.
He's about this tall, and his eyes sparkle
like a little puppy's.
And his shoulders were as wide
as the Pacific Ocean. Whoosh, like that.
-That hurts!
-Young-seo, you can't do that to…
You're going to get into trouble
if you do that to the police.
Come here. I'm so sorry.
Hey! You haven't been hearing what
I've been trying to tell you all night.
Is it so wrong that I want to meet the man
I'm destined to be with one more time?
You've been going on and on
with that nonsense for hours now.
I'll rip your whole mouth off.
Young-seo!
Hey, what's wrong with your mouth?
Young-seo, your mouth's ripped!
-It's ripped open?
-Let me see!
-It's ripped.
-It ripped!
No! Mom, fire, blood, needle!
Say, "Ah!"
I'm sorry, Young-seo!
It hurts. My heart hurts.
-I'm sorry.
-I think I'm going to throw up.
That doesn't sound good at all.
No throwing up.
She's never acted out her whole life,
but now here she is,
driving the dagger
into our hearts with this scene.
-I'm so sorry.
-Oh, it's okay.
I'll take those.
Oh, you can give it here.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll take care of this mess
and make sure they're sorry.
You can leave now.
-Oh, okay.
-Goodbye.
Good night.
-No throwing up.
-I'm sorry.
Take care, then.
Young-seo, you can't throw up.
Let's go for one more round.
Go upstairs right now!
Last night, we…
Let's cut back on drinking from now on.
Shall we?
-Yes.
-Okay.
I love you, Mom.
I love you, Ms. Han.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
About the wedding, we should
probably have it at our hotel, right?
What? The wedding?
Yes. I was going to talk about it
with Chairman Jin,
but he's on a business trip abroad
and isn't coming back until next week.
Does he not know time is of the essence?
You're thinking
about the wedding venue already?
You hate wasting time.
Marriage is already on the table.
The faster we get this going,
the faster I'll get to see
some great-grandkids, right?
The thing is--
That girl used to cause
a scene on blind dates.
But she seems to have fallen in love
at first sight with my dear grandson.
You two are meant to be.
Oh, man.
-Your phone keeps ringing.
-What?
A NEW MESSAGE FROM JIN YOUNG-SEO
Indeed, she seems to have fallen
head over heels. She wants to see me.
Really? Let me see.
Hey, show me.
Let's eat.
I got a text from President Kang.
"I'll tell you where we'll meet later."
Don't mess this up. Don't go around saying
anything stupid and blowing my cover.
Who showed up to the blind date again?
I hired her through an agency to act
the part. She's a complete stranger.
-Happy now?
-Just go and tell him that, okay?
-Okay. Let's go.
-Let's go.
It'll finally be over.
Why does she want to see you again?
I thought she ended things last night.
-Isn't it obvious?
-What is?
She realized I'm
too good of a man to reject
just to rebel against her father.
I don't think that's the case.
She said that you're cheesy
and that she doesn't like your face
because it looks like an archaeopteryx.
-Then why would she ask to see me again?
-I have no idea.
Wow, Ms. Jin really has a keen eye.
You really look like an archaeopter--
Stop talking about the archaeopteryx.
-They look exactly the same!
-Hey, what did you just say?
Wait, Mr. Cha!
That looks good.
Right, about the mackerel.
How's the curing coming along?
-I'll pan-fry them today.
-Okay
I guess I'll stink all day again.
If I knew I'd be doing this all day,
I never would've started working here.
I know, right?
Please, Ms. Shin,
don't say things you don't mean.
You're always so excited
when you're working.
-Me? I am?
-Yes.
Wow, I can't believe it.
The more I find out about President Kang,
the more I learn we have a lot in common.
What do you have in common?
Rumor has it that
President Kang was the top of his class
when he was at Harvard.
I was also the top of my class
for a semester in college.
Also, he got a gold medal at the Amateur
National Track and Field Championships.
You all know, right?
I am Gye Bin, the winner
of our company field day relay race.
Hey, what do you call this?
Parallel universes.
How can we be so alike?
You know what? Then I have so many things
in common with Gianna Jun.
We both have two eyes, one nose, one mouth
and we're both women.
How dare you compare yourself
to my Gianna?
Then why do you keep saying things
to tick me off?
I know you have
no intention of ever getting married.
Here they go again.
To other female employees,
it's really useful information.
It could be an opportunity
to climb up the ladder, you know?
What?
Sure, okay.
Goodness, how do you always know
exactly what to say
-to get your face smashed in?
-What?
Stop saying "female employees."
They're just employees.
Don't you know that's sexist?
And, what, climb up the ladder?
The only thing that's climbing
is my blood pressure.
So stop it
and get those invoices submitted.
That's why she's still single.
INCOMING CALL
MIN-WOO
Hi, Min-woo.
-Min-woo?
-Oh, okay.
-Ms. Yeo.
-Yes?
May I step out for a moment?
Who was that on the phone?
You sound so happy.
Yes, it's…
my fling.
Wow, that was a loud whisper.
Okay.
What? Min-woo's her fling?
A fling.
Ms. Kim.
I'm asking because I'm curious,
but what exactly is a fling?
Is that what you call the phase
before you start to actually date…
I'm sorry.
I should ask someone who'd know.
I'm really sorry.
What do you mean?
I have a lot of experience in that area.
Feel free to ask me.
No, I'm sorry for asking.
What? Are those two really a thing?
There's no way.
They've only met a couple of times
during our team dinners.
Right.
What's with all the touching?
Were they close enough to exchange gifts?
He's leaving?
Wait!
What do I do?
Ha-ri, you're so pathetic.
What are you even doing?
Have you taken care of that thing
we talked about yesterday?
-Yes, sir. It's taken care of.
-Excuse me.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Sir, are you all right?
Who was it?
Who threw this at my face?
Sir, your nose is bleeding.
My nose is bleeding?
That woman in the white lab coat.
Oh, come on!
President Kang!
Please open this for me.
I'm so out of breath.
What, why?
Stop right there!
Damn it!
That little… Damn it!
Damn.
President Kang!
Everyone's going to see.
Oh, no!
What are you doing here?
She must be a researcher.
The Food Product Development Team
is upstairs.
No, she went this way.
This slipper belongs to you, doesn't it?
I'm asking you why you threw this at me.
I didn't mean to.
It was a mistake, I slipped.
SENIOR RESEARCHER
SHIN HA-RI
Ms. Shin Ha-ri, I can't hear
a word you're saying.
I didn't mean to. It was a mistake.
I slipped. I'm sorry.
Then why did you run?
I can't say it's because I thought you
might recognize my face!
I was surprised
because your nose was bleeding. I'm sorry.
Put it back on.
Thank you.
The Bucket List Fish was your work, right?
Yes.
And the vegetarian
dumplings campaign too, right?
Yes.
Huh? That proposal wasn't ever approved.
How did you--
I remember
because the idea was pretty good.
Right?
If you think about it,
my ideas were ahead of their time.
It would be perfect now.
Being vegan is trending these days.
Vegetable dumplings without calories!
It would have been popular
with the vegetarians
as well as with anybody on a diet.
It's such a shame.
My mackerel!
The curing should be done by now!
I'll be going now.
She acts awfully strange,
but I like the way she works.
What's up? What's bothering you?
What? Oh, no.
This is no time to be working.
Do you know what happened?
Some employee threw a slipper
at President Kang
in the lobby on the first floor.
He even got a nosebleed!
Hey, Ms. Kim. You were
on the first floor earlier, right?
Did you see anything?
I didn't see anything.
You said you were going to see your fling.
What's with all the head banging?
As of today, I'm no longer in a fling.
The guy I was talking about
was Chef Lee Min-woo.
Oh, Min-woo?
You're talking about Ms. Shin's friend
who was at the restaurant
when we were having our company dinner?
The handsome guy?
Oh, that guy?
Wait, but you barely know him.
Well, he was totally my type,
so I texted him first,
and I even left him a present
at his restaurant.
Then why is it already over?
You even gave him a gift.
Right.
He said he felt uncomfortable or whatever.
Oh, I see.
I'm going to go take out the mackerel now.
Can't you read the room?
What? What did I do?
Don't you know Chef Lee
already has someone he's interested in?
No way.
Ms. Yeo, have you no shame?
He's young enough to be your nephew.
Don't even think about it!
Don't you click those pincers at me!
Not me.
Damn it, that's hot!
Let's see, how about here?
What's this?
Who the hell parked like this?
Oh, come on.
Why is everything
in my life so difficult these days?
Aren't you the guy
from the convenience store?
Oh, hello. How did you remember?
It'd be hard to forget anybody who looks
as good as you do.
I'm good at remembering people's faces.
Anyway, I'm in a bit of a hurry right now.
Call me.
Please. Call me.
Team Leader Jin Young-seo
from Marine Group?
-You're Jin Young-seo?
-Yes.
Is there a problem?
There is a big problem.
Ms. Fake Jin Young-seo.
Don't you know that it's a crime
to use someone else's name and identity?
What? What do you mean someone else's?
Who are you anyway?
I went on a blind date with
the real Jin Young-Seo a few days ago.
Are you saying you're Kang Tae-moo?
Why does my man of destiny
have to see me like this?
What?
No, it's nothing.
Ms. Jin.
Who's the fake Jin Young-seo
who went on the blind date with me?
I don't know. I hired her through
an agency to act the part.
I don't know her face or name.
She's a complete stranger.
A complete stranger?
Yes.
But the bag that the woman brought
to the date looked exactly that one.
What?
There's no way.
Hers was Chanel,
and this is Saint Laurent.
They're two very different bags.
You have no clue.
Chanel and Saint Laurent?
I thought she was a complete stranger.
How did you know what kind of bag she had?
Right, how did I?
The elders in our families
will be very angry with you
when they realize what you've been up to.
Are you okay with that?
Are you going to tell them
the whole truth?
Can't you just say it didn't work out
once we saw each other again?
And we decided not to get married?
Then, before any of that,
bring her here first.
Who?
The woman
who I almost married.
Why isn't she responding to her texts?
Yep, it's all good now. Don't worry.
What a relief.
This is driving me crazy.
What do you expect me to do?
JOY ART ACADEMY
Here's the bud,
and right here are the leaves.
Oh, it's fine. I scribbled more
than he did anyway. Here you go.
That woman was Jin Young-seo, huh?
You're back?
Please leave my house alone.
How can I leave it alone?
Why do you always leave such
a mess, Sung-hoon?
-Did you buy what I asked for?
-Here.
And let me tell you again.
It's not a mess. I just have my own way
of organizing things.
Unpack them.
Now that you've cleaned and cooked,
-do you feel less stressed?
-Yeah.
You sure have a weird way of de-stressing.
How is it weird?
I put in time and effort,
and the result reflects that.
It's productive.
Anyway, since the Jin Young-seo
who came to the blind date was a fake,
I guess the marriage is off.
Why would that make any sense?
She dared to waste my time
and made me say all those things.
I guess the last thing Ms. Jin wanted
was to be in an arranged marriage, too.
It's not something to be so mad about.
I'm talking about the fake Ms. Jin,
not the real one.
She was just a replacement and said what?
Cheesy? An archaeopteryx?
That's a weird direction
you're taking with your anger.
I can't forgive her.
I'll have my revenge soon enough.
When did you get here?
Just now.
Hey, did President Kang
get mad at you for trying to fool him?
What?
It's just, there was a rumor at work
that he's a really scary guy.
He fired executives who betrayed him.
Let's stop talking
about what's already over.
Why don't we blow off some stress
and go out somewhere?
Where?
Go ahead and try on anything you want.
That one?
Next.
I think this one looks the best!
What's gotten into you?
Buying me all these clothes?
I know that you've been stressed
these days because of me.
I'm getting all pampered for going out
on one little blind date for you?
Wait, are you--
Am I what?
Don't ask me to go on
another blind date for you.
I'm not going to do it ever again!
Don't worry, I won't ever ask again.
Make her look nice, please!
Make her shine!
-Hey.
-Yeah.
Say cheese!
Let's do this!
Are you sure that beauty salon is really
the one celebrities use?
Look at how intense my makeup is.
That's because I asked them
to do it like that.
What's that supposed to mean?
Ha-ri. Listen to me carefully.
-President Kang will be here soon.
-What? Who's coming?
I didn't have a choice!
He realized we were friends
and asked to meet you.
Then you should've
pretended not to know me!
But then he said he'd find out on his own!
What if he finds out you're his employee?
You could've at least warned me.
Then you wouldn't have come here.
Anyway, he thinks you owe him an apology.
-Just say you're sorry.
-What?
What's the worst that can happen?
Okay, I'm going now.
-You're leaving?
-Oh, right!
Don't forget and be sure to wear the wig.
-A wig?
-Sorry.
-I'm sorry!
-Wait, Young-seo!
Young-seo!
I knew I had a bad feeling about this!
Damn it.
Hold on!
What do I do?
I don't know!
Oh, damn it.
Why did this have to spill right now?
Oh, thank you.
Oh, my.
We meet again, Ms. Fake Jin Young-seo.
You work at a fried chicken shop?
What?
Oh, that.
I can just call and check.
My family runs a fried chicken… shop, yes.
Damn it, I told him where I live, too.
How much?
Plain fried chicken is 15,000 won
and the spicy one is 17,000 won.
I wasn't talking about--
About the chicken.
How much did you get paid
to impersonate Jin Young-seo?
That's…
So…
Just lay it out honestly.
I kept on telling her I couldn't do it,
that I really couldn't do it,
but then she just kept telling me
she would pay me 800,000 won.
So, that's how it all happened.
You tried to scam me
for merely 800,000 won?
Going as a replacement
isn't technically a scam, is it?
You pretended to be another person.
You deliberately wasted someone's
precious time for your own benefit.
If that's not a scam, what is it?
I'm sorry.
I urgently needed some money,
and it wasn't an amount that I could
handle with my monthly paycheck.
I thought you were just a regular
old scammer, but you have a job, too?
You've got some skills, yeah?
Oh, I mean it's just
a small, medium-sized company.
Yeah, real small…
And that company is actually yours.
I wonder if he brought that
handsome secretary along again.
No. This is no time to think about men
when you've just thrown your friend
to the wolves.
I'm sorry, dear friend.
Anyway, he thinks you owe him an apology.
Just say you're sorry.
I didn't do anything wrong
besides hiding the fact
that I'm an employee of his.
But it'd be my loss if he finds out
who I am just because I made him mad.
I know that a simple apology
won't be enough.
I wish I could make it up to you
for all of the time you wasted
and for your hurt feelings,
but there isn't a way to do that.
And it's not like I can pay you back
in money or gifts,
as you already have so
much more than I do.
What I can do is promise that I'll do
everything in my power to help you out
if you ever need a favor.
Are you still mad?
In what way,
do I look like an archaeopteryx?
Sorry?
Oh, is that why you're angry?
It's not that I'm angry,
it's just that I've never heard
such nonsense before,
so I was caught off-guard, yes.
Oh, that.
I just said whatever popped into my head
because I wanted you
to stop asking me to marry you.
Whatever popped into your head?
But the resemblance is there.
Your small face, your sharp eyes,
and your lanky limbs.
No one has ever told you that?
Didn't I just tell you
that I've never heard it before?
Oh, right.
I'm sorry.
That's really why he got so angry?
Wow, hold a grudge much?
Well,
if there's not much else for us
to talk about,
would it be okay
if we wrapped things up about now?
We're still looking for part-timers
at my family's chicken shop,
so I help out in the evenings.
I think it'll be best for me
to get going--
INCOMING CALL
DON'T ANSWER
Save my name again.
And pick up when I call from now on.
If you don't answer my calls,
or try to disappear…
I will come and find you.
Okay.
Also, what's your actual name?
My name?
Shin Ha--
If I give him my real name,
he might recognize me later on.
Geum… hui.
Geum-hui.
SHIN GEUM-HUI
Archaeopteryx.
I wonder if Ms. Geum-hui
can manage a smile today?
I'll have the cheese pork cutlet.
Yes, sir.
What kind of rich folks would meet up
at a pork cutlet franchise
to see all their in-laws?
Either way, I'm still jealous.
It'd be nice to meet some in-laws
at a pork cutlet restaurant.
I'm home.
You're just getting back?
Everything went well with Ms. Jin?
So what about the wedding?
Both of our families should
meet first, right?
I decided not to marry Ms. Jin Young-seo.
What? What do you--
Well, that's what happened,
so please don't bring her up anymore.
That little--
I can't agree to this marriage.
No, I won't agree.
The person I really love is Geum-hui.
-Shin Geum-hui.
-Gwang-bok!
You dare insult my daughter all because
of some girl from the fried chicken shop?
That must have hurt. I bet the crust
on that cutlet was really crispy.
Anyway, whether it's in real life
or on television,
why is it so hard to get married,
these days?
Shin Geum-hui.
BE STRONG, GEUM-HUI
Why did I suddenly think of that name?
I feel like I've heard it somewhere.
Shin Geum-hui.
Your call has been forwarded to voicemail…
Wow, she's turned her phone off, huh?
You just wait until I find you,
Young-seo. I will destroy you.
Ha-ri, you're back!
Jin Young-seo!
Calm down.
You! You're a really bad person!
Hey, what are you doing?
Please!
I'm sorry.
I didn't know my phone was turned off.
I swear I wasn't ignoring you
on purpose, really.
Save it!
Good thing I was quick
and gave him a fake name.
Or else, he could've fired me
then and there!
What were you thinking, taking me there?
I'm really sorry.
You saw him, how charismatic he can be!
I didn't have a choice.
At least he doesn't know
that you're his employee so--
But he found out that my family
runs a fried chicken shop!
What? Wait, how?
I felt bad about skipping the birthday
party that my coworkers threw for me,
so I was bringing some coupons
and dropped them.
Why would you bring those coupons
with you? You thoughtless idiot!
You have no right to be yelling
at me like that!
It's all your fault!
Wearing this apron isn't going to--
Ha-ri!
What are you doing? Why are you grabbing
Young-seo by the collar?
-No, this is--
-I'm all right, Mrs. Han.
Also, don't scold Ha-ri, please.
It's all my fault, and I deserve it.
I mean, how bad could it have been?
You can't grab your friend
by the collar like this!
You and your temper! Let go now!
-Let go of her, come on!
-What?
Mom, you don't know anything!
If you like Young-seo so much, why don't
you just raise her instead of me?
-I mean, really--
-Look at that temper.
Why do you have to be so mean?
Mrs. Han! It's all my fault, I'm sorry!
-Wow, look at you.
-What?
Both of you, stop!
Who did she get that hot temper
from, anyway? Really!
Does she really not know
who she gets it from?
Why can't she get along with her friend?
You should count yourself lucky
Young-seo stays by your side.
If I had a daughter like Young-seo,
I'd be so happy!
I know, right?
Mom, don't you wish that
you had a daughter like Young-seo?
Do you want me to seduce her?
To have a "daughter"-in-law. It'd be nice.
Even if you tried,
you think that would work?
What do you mean, a "daughter"-in-law?
It's just a daughter-in-law!
Just fold your laundry.
You should take this chance
to buy this kimchi product.
This early in the morning?
I told them to mind the scheduling.
Call to place--
The archaeopteryx is considered
to be the ancestor of all modern birds.
Fossil samples were discovered
in limestone in Solnhofen, Bavaria.
The archaeopteryx lived at the end
of the Jurassic period, in the southern
part of modern-day Germany.
Freaking Jurassic, damn it.
You can see that the length of the body
is about 30 to 50 centimeters long,
which is about the size of a raven.
This was a bird with a small head
and large eyes…
Hello?
Ms. Geum-hui?
What's he saying?
Why is anyone prank calling at this hour?
It's not a prank call.
Are you still half-asleep? Ms. Geum-hui.
I'm not Geum--
Sorry, you just surprised me.
Why did you call?
I just called to make sure
you didn't get a new number
to cut me off. That's all.
Okay.
Hello?
What?
It's four in the morning.
Has he lost his mind?
What the heck? I'm totally awake now.
Is he insane?
This guy is so annoying! Really!
He's so annoying.
Here, you can observe its teeth.
An archaeopteryx?
There are three-clawed…
I hope she gets a terrible night's sleep.
On the tail, there are 20 to 21 tail--
Why are you yawning
first thing in the morning?
You didn't sleep well?
I just had trouble going back
to sleep in the middle of the night.
Okay.
Did you all hear? You haven't, right?
Again, I'm the only one
who's heard, right?
Okay. Focus, everyone.
Apparently, President Kang
went on a blind date.
Jeez, what's the big deal?
It has nothing to do with us.
There you go again.
You have to see the big picture here.
It has everything to do with us!
Rich people will always stick together.
There might be a merger.
That'll have a huge impact
on stock prices.
You barely have a few dozen shares
of the company stock.
Why are you making such a big deal of it
as if you're some major shareholder?
I have a grand total of 50 shares.
That all adds up, you know?
Anyway, stop talking about President Kang.
He may be the president of our company,
but he's someone we might never run into.
Are you a pro-wrestler?
How are you so strong?
Right?
Please, help me so I never have
to run into that man, dear Buddha.
Dear God.
You asked for me?
Yes. With the factory in Ilsan,
when are we planning to restart
the second production line?
They said it would take at least a week
to finish all of the replacement work.
And today's the first day at work
for Mr. Hwang, right?
Mr. Park's replacement?
Let's have lunch with him today.
Actually, your schedule has changed
starting from lunch today.
What? What do you mean?
Without so much as a word to me?
The order came from the chairman himself.
I'm scheduling the dates for you again.
What?
So that's how it's going to be, huh?
Han Min-hui. Daemang Industries.
She majored in piano
at the Juilliard School of Music,
and she's currently working toward
a doctorate at Seoul National University.
People say it's a shame
that I have to get married
with this career.
But I think bringing a child
that has my good genetics into this world
and raising it is also worthwhile.
The second daughter of the Minister of
Justice. Graduate of Harvard Med School.
Seeing as she's from Harvard too,
you two should have a lot in common.
You know Professor Albert, right?
Yes, he was my advisor.
He taught a business course
that I took as an elective,
and I remember him speaking
very highly of you.
Your senior thesis…
-Mr. Kang? I've heard a lot about you.
-You're even better looking than I heard.
And you're so tall.
I love how you look so calm.
-You're my type.
When I told my family about you…
All the elders were thrilled.
This is the first time
I've felt like this, so…
-my heart is fluttering.
-My heart is fluttering.
Oh, look at me rambling on.
Do you think there's any other person
who goes on ten blind dates in a day?
Probably not.
You'll set a new record for the most blind
dates in the shortest amount of time.
You hit the wrong button.
Why did you press the roof?
I didn't press the wrong one.
It's not over yet.
What?
Her name is Yoko Hitori,
and her Korean name is Oh Eun-ji.
A third-generation immigrant,
and the second-in-line for Hitori Foods.
Did any of the ladies today
catch your eye?
-Not at all.
-What?
They all seemed a lot better
than the fake Jin Young-seo,
who you decided to marry at first glance.
At least the fake Jin Young-seo
wasn't boring.
How can they all say
the exact same things?
That is true.
She sure was different from the others.
President Kang, your nose is bleeding.
My nose is bleeding?
Damn it.
Stupid nosebleeds.
You're late.
How were the blind dates?
Don't you think this is a bit much?
Do you have any idea
how many blind dates I just went on?
You went over to Japan
to make it to number 11.
How was today? Did you like
any of the ladies you met today?
I can't believe you.
Stop overreacting.
You're the one who got me all excited,
saying you would marry Jin Young-seo.
And then, what? You call it off?
-Are you toying with your grandfather?
-That's not it.
Stop making excuses and keep your promise!
Meet the rest tomorrow, up to number 20.
And if there's still no lady
that you like,
I'll find a year's worth of eligible women
you can go on dates with.
LIST OF BLIND DATE CANDIDATES
I have a woman who I want to marry.
What?
You have someone you want to marry?
Yes.
You're always buried in your work.
When did you have the time--
No matter how busy I am,
I still have the time to meet women.
You should've said that
from the beginning.
Then why did you go on
all those blind dates?
And why would you say all that nonsense
about marrying Ms. Young-seo?
The truth is, we broke up for a little bit
because we had a fight.
So I did it out of anger.
Is he telling the truth?
You should thank Mr. Cha.
He's the reason we made up
and got back together.
Yes, sir. I tried very hard.
So when will you introduce her to me?
I'll set up a meeting in the near future.
Set a date immediately.
I need to ask her when she's available.
That means no more blind dates
for me, right?
Sure.
If you had told me beforehand,
I wouldn't have set up
such an overwhelming schedule like today.
So you're aware that it was overwhelming?
All right, do what you need to do.
I'll be going now.
Be good.
President Kang?
How could you tell that kind of lie
when you don't have
a woman you're marrying?
How will you get out of this one?
What do you think?
I'm going to tell the person in charge
to take responsibility.
INCOMING CALL
ARCHAEOPTERYX
What is this? I already apologized
and settled the whole thing.
So annoying.
-Hello?
-Let's meet after you get off of work.
What? Why?
I'm busy.
-Should I go to your house, then?
-What? No!
I mean, I'm going to be late today.
I'm working overtime, so I'll be at work.
Where do you work, Ms. Shin?
Where do I work?
It's pretty far from Seoul, actually.
Far, where? I even went to Japan today.
Is it farther than Japan?
What?
What? Ilsan?
Why Ilsan all of a sudden?
I don't know. The words popped out.
Wow, seriously?
So what are you going to do?
I'm meeting him
at some coffee shop near the subway.
I'm actually almost there.
I'll call you later. Bye!
What? He's already there?
Hello?
I'm at the coffee shop.
Are you sure you're a regular, here?
-Of course, why?
-Nothing. It just seems a bit strange.
Rainbow Cafe, right? That's the one.
I had coffee there yesterday, too.
Thank you.
I'm here. Wait just a second.
Where's Rainbow Cafe?
You're really a regular here?
Yes, I am. I really like the vibe here.
Mom, he pushed me!
I'm not your mom.
I'm so sorry.
You like this kind of vibe?
Well, sure, there's the vibe,
but the coffee is really good here.
Could you make it quick?
I need to head home soon.
This isn't the place to say such things,
but I want us to start dating.
With marriage in mind.
What?
Did you fall in love at first sight when
you saw me on our blind date or something?
It wasn't my plan for that to happen.
You're getting ahead of yourself.
I'm not saying
that we should actually date.
Just pretend like we are, Ms. Shin.
What?
I won't do it. You've been calling me
a fraud and an imposter,
and now you're asking me
to do it all over again?
What else am I supposed to do?
You're the best person for the job.
The best person for the job?
You've proven your acting skills
on our date last time.
You already know my situation,
so I don't need to explain.
And the secret is safe with you.
Most importantly,
you wanted to repay your debt.
Not to mention
all the precious time I'll save.
It's a win-win situation, is it not?
I don't care who wins what.
I don't want to lie to other people again.
I'll just forget
we ever had this conversation.
You said you received 800,000 won?
I'll double it.
Double it?
And that's every time
you meet with my grandfather.
He's a suspicious man, so it'll take
more than a couple of meetings.
When I look back
at the short life that I've led so far,
I spent more time in debt
than I ever spent being happy.
Mom, Dad.
We have nothing to say as your parents.
STUDENT LOANS, CREDIT CARDS,
COLLATERAL LOANS, NEGATIVE ACCOUNTS
DEBT
PAYCHECK FROM KBBQ RESTAURANT
BALANCE -2,89M WON
PAYCHECK FROM BAR
DEBT
BALANCE -2M WON
PAYCHECK FROM LOADING AND UNLOADING BOXES
Bye, debt!
Mom, Dad.
I got into a major company!
I'm sorry, Ha-ri.
Ha-ri.
ECONOMIC DAILY
CHICKEN INDUSTRY IN PERIL
EPIC FAIL
I might be able to
get rid of my debts at once.
Should I just go for it?
No.
Money is important,
but he's the company president.
Have you made up your mind?
I don't think I can do it. I'm sorry.
When you were apologizing
for deceiving me,
you said you were willing
to do anything to help me.
Were those empty words?
-What? No, I meant that.
-Then do this for me.
This is the only thing
that you could help me with
that's within your power.
I mean…
Make sure to eat well.
Are you back, sweetie?
Hi.
-Welcome--
-This is crazy.
Shin Geum-hui!
Refreshing beer for the table!
How dare you try to take
my daughter's lover?
I'm sorry. I have nothing to say--
Then don't speak!
Shut your mouth!
You have no shame.
Oh, my. Last week Gwang-bok was
getting slapped with a pork cutlet,
and this week, Geum-hui's getting
slapped with a chicken leg?
How could she do that to such a nice girl?
You think a rich family would
ever accept a girl like Geum-hui?
Her family just runs
a local fried chicken shop.
Oh, my gosh.
What's wrong with that?
I didn't mean Ha-ri.
We're talking about the TV show.
All those rubbish TV shows need to go
off the air, you hear?
The love story where a poor girl
falls in love with a superrich guy?
It's not realistic at all.
Mom. That unrealistic love story
is happening to me right now.
What? Is it that bastard Tae-moo again?
Hi, Min-woo.
Hey, I'm going to forget your face.
Why haven't you stopped by?
I've been a bit busy at work.
What's wrong with your voice?
Did something happen?
Work has been stressing me out a bit.
Yeah.
Okay, I'll swing by soon.
All right.
Okay.
Kang Tae-moo, that bastard.
I'm so stressed about that archaeopteryx.
I can't focus on anything.
Hey! I could have gotten hurt!
Jeez.
Rich people are people too.
Why do they only ever scream and yell?
They're always portrayed as the bad guys.
I'm back.
Hey! Did you…
set a date for us
to meet with your girlfriend?
Pardon?
Why are you making that face?
Is something wrong?
No, don't worry. You'll see her then.
Really?
What is it now?
Hello?
Where are you?
Where would I be at this hour?
I'm at home, of course.
Then come down for a second.
I'm in front of your house.
You're in front of my house? Now?
Wait, hold on. Why?
Why would you drop by this late
without telling me?
I was about to go to bed.
It looks like your lights are still on.
Oh, right.
-Would you rather I let myself in?
-No! I'll come out!
You just stay put, okay?
This guy is just so stubborn!
Wait, what do I have to--
First, let's…
Can you even see anything?
I thought you were about to go to bed.
I never let anybody see
what I look like without makeup.
It's like a rule as a woman.
Judging by what you're wearing,
that "rule" doesn't seem to be consistent.
Whatever.
Why did you come all the way here?
I drafted up a contract. Take a look.
And memorize my profile
before you meet my grandfather.
I said I would think about it,
not that I would do it.
I don't think
I have any other options but you.
You said you would repay me.
-So let's do it. A contract relationship.
-No.
Just find some other woman.
Damn it.
Ms. Shin Geum-hui.
Are you really going
to back out like this?
No, that's not what I'm saying.
It's because I really have
a reason I can't do it.
How am I supposed to fool
both the president and chairman
of the company that I work at?
What's your reason? Let's hear it.
So it's--
-Wait, first--
-What are you doing?
Let's talk tomorrow!
Subtitle translation by: Su-in Choi
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs