BUSINESS PROPOSAL
-What are you doing?
-Well, I…
-Hey.
-We'll have to delay
the meeting by an hour.
Mr. Go got into a minor car accident
on his way here.
-Really? Delay it, then.
-Yes, sir.
It's because I have a stye on my eye.
Aren't you going to press a floor?
Oh, right.
Let's attend the tasting event
for the new product lineup then.
Yes, sir.
The tasting event?
FOOD PRODUCT DEVELOPMENT TEAM 1
FOOD PRODUCT DEVELOPMENT TEAM 2
FOOD PRODUCT DEVELOPMENT TEAM 3
Please give us your honest feedback.
Thank you.
-We're Team One.
-We'd really appreciate some feedback.
-Thank you very much.
-Here.
-Please fill out a feedback form.
-Sure.
We're Team One.
-Please enjoy.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
-We're Team One.
-Take it easy.
Chef Lee, you're working so hard
when the other chefs aren't even here.
The other chefs are quite experienced,
but this is a first for me.
We're Team One.
This is white kimchi ravioli.
The president is here.
-Welcome, President Kang.
-He's so hot!
Thank you all for your hard work.
President Kang, how are you?
Sir, you should have told us
that you were coming.
You should always be prepared.
Sir, Team One is always prepared.
Even our chef is here today.
-Is that so?
-Yes, sir.
Let me introduce him to you.
This is Chef Lee Min-woo from M Kitchen.
He developed
the white kimchi ravioli with us.
I'm Kang Tae-moo.
Nice to meet you.
Ta-da!
Is this the white kimchi ravioli?
Yes, sir.
Please give it a try, sir.
Chef Lee.
You don't have a good eye for things.
Pardon?
I heard this was for staff meals.
Why didn't you put something
this delicious on the menu?
That's what you meant?
That was hilarious, sir.
It was something I had whipped together.
But thanks to Ha-ri,
it's our signature dish now.
Right. I read Ms. Shin's proposal.
I could feel her deep trust in you,
Chef Lee.
The two have been good friends
since college, so…
I think
that's why they worked together so well.
Yes, that's right.
Come to think of it, I don't see Ms. Shin.
Ms. Shin, is your stomach okay?
Do you want me to buy you some medicine?
No, I'm all right now.
Hey, how are people
reacting to our ravioli?
Are they saying it's good?
Nobody's responding to me.
Mr. Kang should have left by now.
Should I go back inside?
Did you see President Kang? He's so hot.
That chef was handsome too.
Was his name Lee Min-woo?
Right. But the white kimchi ravioli?
It was my first time trying it,
but I liked it.
Me too. I think it was
the best dish there.
Your bruise is getting worse.
Do you want something to put on it?
Don't you know me? I'd rather just eat.
I'll be fine.
Oh, right. What are people
saying about the tasting?
Everyone said the food was good,
but I'm not sure if they meant it.
Trust me. The guys at my company
don't sugarcoat things.
They're really picky.
They say it's perfect, taste-wise.
Now it just needs some fine-tuning
as we commercialize it.
Just leave things to me, Chef Lee.
Then I'll do just that, Ms. Shin.
Oh, right!
Where's your review?
What review?
Of the concert you went to.
Yoo-ra was wondering, too.
How was it? Did you have fun?
Yes, I had fun.
Man, I was hoping you would go with a guy.
I bet you went with Young-seo.
I went with a guy.
Really?
Who?
Just someone I got to know by chance.
You never told me you were seeing someone.
Do you even know what kind of guy he is?
Yes, well…
You're too naive
to even get a good read on guys.
Bring him with you sometime, will you?
I'll take a look at him for you.
I can take care of myself, Min-woo.
So take care of your girlfriend now,
instead of your friends.
You two got back together
after breaking up.
Pay more attention to her.
Why is Young-seo so late?
She's so impatient!
I'm here.
He looks a lot like the guy
who lives next door.
Wait!
That is him!
YOUNG-SEO
It's President Kang!
Sir.
Hello. I didn't know you were coming.
After the tasting event, I was even
more curious about your cooking, Chef Lee.
I'm glad you came, then.
I'll whip up something delicious for you.
Just as expected, this place is popular.
Please, have a seat. This way.
Oh, right, Ha-ri is here too.
That's weird.
She was just here a minute ago.
Why don't you have a seat?
You'd get sick of me
If we spent all of our days together
I, too…
Hello.
Where are you, Ha-ri?
Oh, apparently there's a big group
at the chicken shop.
I think Young-seo and I
need to go help out.
Hey!
Okay!
Yes, okay. See you!
Hold on,
so the handsome guy you saw
at the convenience store is Secretary Cha?
-Yes.
-And Mr. Cha lives right next door?
Yes.
-Just how do you meet someone like that?
-That's what I'm saying.
Hey, you don't think
I'll run into him here too, do you?
This is driving me nuts.
Just, don't even think about
coming to my apartment for the time being.
Or dress up as Shin Geum-hui if you do.
It's you who needs to be careful.
Don't get all friendly with him and blab
that Shin Ha-ri is actually Shin Geum-hui.
I don't think I'll talk to him again.
So don't worry about that.
-Why?
-Well…
You know how Tae-moo's family and mine are
on bad terms because of the blind date?
So he said he doesn't want to
get involved with me, either.
-What?
-Seriously!
He definitely liked me at first.
No, really!
Hey. You don't believe me?
Wait, what if Tae-moo bad-mouthed me
and told Mr. Cha to avoid me
because I'm completely nuts?
That petty archaeopteryx.
No, no. I don't think President Kang is
the type to talk badly about other people.
He looks a bit cold-hearted,
but he has a considerate side to him too.
Why are you taking Kang Tae-moo's side?
That's suspicious.
It's not. It's just--
You and this supposedly fake relationship,
yet you even went to a concert together.
Have you fallen for him?
It's not like that.
It's just, I didn't know
when I saw him from a distance,
but now that I've seen him up-close,
you know, he's not that bad.
You know, that's all it is…
Really?
-Is that really all there is to it?
-Yes!
That's enough. Let's just order.
-How was your meal?
-I think I know now.
Why Ms. Shin says your food
tastes cheerful and happy, Chef Lee.
I agree.
Thank you. Ha-ri is always
generous with my food.
You're college friends, right?
We met when we were 20,
so we've known each other for 7 years now.
And you've been just friends
this whole time?
Excuse me?
Oh. I apologize
if my question was too personal.
I just thought maybe one of you
could have developed feelings
since you've known each other
for such a long time.
I have no regrets, though.
I was really happy…
for those seven years.
Seven years, huh?
Sir, when you asked Chef Lee
about his relationship with Ms. Shin,
was it because of something you heard?
What do you mean?
I overheard some of the employees talking,
and apparently,
Ms. Shin had a crush on Chef Lee.
Is that so?
I guess there's someone else
like Ms. Shin Geum-hui too.
What now?
Did he just avoid me?
Excuse me!
Wait a second.
Am I a virus or something?
Why are you avoiding me?
You don't even want to take
the same elevator as me now?
-It's not--
-I mean.
how could you so openly avoid me?
-Do you not have any manners?
-I wasn't avoiding you.
It was because of this.
I thought you might be bothered
by the smell of the trash.
I was mistaken, then. I'm sorry.
Well, then.
Wait a second.
It's true that what I did
to President Kang was wrong.
That's why I apologized to him.
But that's between Mr. Kang and me.
It doesn't have anything to do with you.
Since we're already in this position,
even if we can't be friends,
can't we be cool and say hi
when we run into each other?
I'm sorry.
I've never been a "cool" person.
He's stomping on my pride.
Is he President Kang's younger brother
or something?
Why is he so damn loyal?
Yes, sir, I've just arrived.
I'll go right up. Yes, sir.
TRUE LIGHT FOUNDATION FOR SOCIAL WELFARE
TRUE LIGHT CHILDREN'S HOME
What are you doing here?
Just looking.
You've left this place exactly as it was.
Of course.
My grandfather really
wants you to move back in.
So do I. Are you really not going to?
No, never.
I don't want to suffer
when I'm at home too.
Suffer?
Hey, what have I ever done to you?
How long has it been
since we all ate together like this?
This place finally feels like a home.
It really does.
Right?
Now, if I just had a granddaughter-in-law
like Ms. Geum-hui
along with some adorable
great-grandchildren,
I'd die a happy man
even if I died tomorrow.
You've been saying that
ever since I turned 20.
Aren't you tired of it?
What's the point of being superrich?
All I ever do is eat by myself
in this empty house like a lonely old man.
Don't you know eating alone
is trendy these days?
That's why our products are selling well.
You always have to have the last word.
Either get married by the year's end,
or we're all eating here together
twice a week.
Grandfather, twice a week is too much. My…
My schedule is packed and…
And my place is far away, too.
I was so tired when I got up this morning.
Now that you mention it,
move back in, Sung-hoon.
Look at you. You moved out
the minute you graduated from college.
Now you're acting like even having
a meal together is something so difficult.
And you call yourselves my grandsons?
How's my schedule this week?
You're free Friday morning.
Should we schedule our next meal then?
Hey, let me look at that.
Tae-moo, do you know
what day this Saturday is?
-What? This Saturday?
-Yes!
-What was that?
-What are you doing?
I can't believe you forgot, you punk.
How could you forget a day like that?
Look!
29TH
SATURDAY
PRESIDENT KANG AND MS. SHIN GEUM-HUI'S
ONE-YEAR ANNIVERSARY
Will you only come to your senses
after Geum-hui dumps you again?
How can you forget a one-year anniversary?
You bastard. You little brat.
Look at you, I bet you'd even forget to
show up at my funeral.
How could you say something like that?
It's not that I forgot--
Then?
Why did you schedule something else
on that day?
I told you, that's…
Cancel everything.
Cancel everything and schedule
a date with Ms. Geum-hui.
I'll make a reservation for you.
Go on, you.
Manager Oh! It's me, Da-goo.
I'm sorry. I had marked it on the calendar
just in case the chairman asked.
What should we do?
Your schedule that day is tight.
No, we can always move things around.
He's okay with changing his schedule?
NAMHAE
Gosh, what are you doing?
That's like putting lipstick on a pig.
It might not make me more handsome,
but at least
I can make myself look average.
They're filming
the entire research process
to upload it
on the company's YouTube account.
This is the least I can do,
don't you think?
Maybe I should have gotten
my hair and makeup done too.
It's fine.
They'll be mainly focused on the chefs.
Researchers like us
will barely be in the shot.
We're here. Let's all get off the bus.
Let's get off.
Okay.
Move.
-That way.
-Okay.
Thank you.
Gosh, I'm nervous.
This is so nice.
Thank you.
What's with all the bags?
This way.
Oh, this looks like a nice spot.
Here.
-You can put those bags here.
-Oh, sure.
Can you check that we packed
the right number of lab coats?
There's no view quite like this
in all the eight provinces of Korea.
It's perfect for de-stressing.
For sure. You have this sweeping farmland,
with those vast mountains as a backdrop,
and the ocean beyond that.
It's a shame that we don't have
anyone else to share this view with.
Stop beating around the bush
and give it to me straight.
What are you saying?
Chairman Kang, why don't we just bulldoze
all of this and build a resort here?
A resort?
Look at the land here.
All we're doing with it
is commercial farming.
Imagine a golf course here
and a ski resort
by the mountains over there.
We could fill the whole place up
with our subsidiary franchises.
Wouldn't that be something?
Why is that idea skipping over
President Kang and coming straight to me?
We submitted a business proposal,
but he shot it down almost immediately.
Is that so?
President Kang is still young
and inexperienced,
so he can't make
a bold move like you'd do.
He's not interested in long-term plans
with guaranteed profits like this.
All he does is play house with his chefs.
So, if you were to directly suggest, sir--
You! Do you want President Kang
to fire you too?
Sir?
You've been buying
the land here bit by bit.
Didn't you think I'd know?
Chairman Kang, that's not--
It seems to me
like you're trying to make a buck
by raising the real estate
prices around here.
Stop it with your ridiculous ideas
and just support President Kang
as he plays house!
Chairman Kang,
this is all a misunderstanding.
All they ever do is try to find ways
to fill their own pockets.
Hold on. Stop the car.
Here are the premium ingredients…
That go food product researchers
have picked from the farm themselves…
To present to the chef!
Oh wait, it's that way.
Cut!
-Hey, Jeong-hwan.
-Yes, sir.
-Jeong-hwan!
-Yes, I'm coming!
What's with the actor?
Wasn't I quite good?
-It was a bit awkward.
-Okay.
Do I need to put more into it?
How can you mess up a line
this short, over ten times?
What was the point of the makeup?
Your acting is still crap.
It's just because I'm camera shy.
Are you taking more calming pills?
He knows that's not candy, right?
If Ms. Shin's eye wasn't like that,
we would have switched you out right away.
Whatever! It's not like
we're filming an epic here.
I can take care of myself,
so don't you worry about a thing!
Don't say such stupid things!
All right, everybody. Stand by, please.
-Okay!
-Okay.
Oh, Ms. Shin.
Do it right!
Am I that bad?
-You got this.
-Yes, I got this.
Let's do it, everybody!
Ready, and cue!
Here are the premium ingredients…
That go food researchers
picked from the farm themselves…
To present to the chef!
Nice catch!
-Chairman Kang.
-Chairman Kang!
-You're all working hard, I see.
My gosh!
Be careful, there.
Oh, here it is. Here it is.
Oh, come on.
Why did this thing get bigger?
Thank you.
Sure.
-Thank you.
-I'll have the chamomile.
Chamomile is perfect for this setting.
-I hope you enjoy it.
-Thank you.
Why did he have to drive past
our shooting location?
He won't recognize me, will he?
It's my first time
seeing the chairman this close.
So Ms. Yeo and Chairman Kang are close?
No, they're not close at all.
She's barely seen him this close-up.
Sucking up is all part of the job,
you know.
It's difficult to work with President Kang
because he's quite strict, isn't it?
Not at all.
Since he knows the entire process
from the ground up better than anyone,
communication is smooth,
and it's more rewarding.
You don't say?
What?
By the way,
what's this weird noise
I've been hearing for a while now?
Oh, I think you're right.
What a weird noise.
Hey, it looks like
somebody left their phone here.
Oh, I think this belongs
to our employee, Ms. Shin.
Oh, really?
Ms. Shin!
-Me?
-Yes.
-What for?
-Come on, quickly.
What?
Come.
You called for me?
Ms. Shin, I think this phone
belongs to you.
Oh, my. Yes, that's mine. Thank you.
Hold on, I think somebody's calling.
"Archaeopteryx?"
ARCHAEOPTERYX
Oh, no!
I'll give it to you
if there's any leftover.
What's wrong with her?
She didn't even thank me.
Come on.
Why did he have to
pick the worst time to call me?
Why aren't you picking up?
It's an emergency, so call me back.
The situation here
is much more of an emergency!
Where am I?
RESTROOM
Oh, the bathroom!
PRESIDENT KANG TAE-MOO
Hello.
What emergency? What's going on?
Never mind that. Why didn't you pick up?
It's against company policy
to be on our phones during work hours.
What? What kind of company does that?
Anyway, what is this about?
Would it kill you
to exchange pleasantries first?
How have you been?
How's your eye doing? And so on.
Oh, sorry. I just have a lot
going on at the moment.
My eye is fine.
Do you know what day this Saturday is?
This Saturday?
Saturday?
Isn't that our fake one-year anniversary?
You're better than me.
I'd forgotten about it.
Well, I've always been good
at memorizing stuff, you know.
What about it, though?
My grandfather found out,
so things got a bit complicated.
Your grandfather?
Do you want to
meet for dinner today?
Oh, but I'm on a business trip right now.
A business trip?
Yes, they scheduled it last minute.
That's a shame then.
Oh, and it turns out
that song is rather popular.
What song?
The song that you've set
as your ringback tone.
I've been hearing it
play all over the place.
I'll call you tomorrow, then.
Okay.
What company bans people
from picking up their phones
and sends an employee with an injured eye
on a business trip?
Sir, are you feeling all right?
You're sweating all of a sudden.
No, it's…
My stomach is…
Oh, maybe it's because
you suddenly had cold food. I can…
I'll get you something warm.
Well, instead of that
I just want to go to the bathroom.
My goodness.
Hello, sir.
It's an honor to have you here, sir.
I woke up this morning
knowing today would be “eye-opening.”
"Eye-opening"?
Oh, man, my stomach.
Yes, sir! “Waking up” is “eye-opening.”
"Eye-opening…"
You've been a big inspiration to me, sir!
I used to be afraid of hurdles in life,
but I “got over” them! Salute!
You're a bit young to be making
dad jokes. Even I don't do those.
God, my stomach.
If you thought this was the end,
you're wrong!
Wrong.
Listen, my stomach hurts.
I have a few more jokes about
how I'm not unemployed thanks to you, sir,
but none of them "work"!
Oh, my stomach.
Hey, I've got a joke about construction,
but I'm still "working on it."
Where can I find a bathroom around here?
So my ringback tone was still that song?
I'd forgotten about it.
But how do I cancel this?
-Oh, man.
-Right this way, sir.
Why is it so far?
Here…
Wait! One second, sir.
Ms. Shin! That's you in there, right?
I saw you running over here.
Make it quick and come out, okay?
Okay, I'm coming out.
Okay. Sir, your bathroom is ready.
Then good luck with your number two, sir.
To healthy bowels!
Hey, look here.
Why did you go back inside?
-Hey!
-What do I do?
For God's sake. There's only one stall.
-What do I do? Oh, my stomach.
-Damn it.
This is bad.
Hey, I really need to go.
Could you hurry up a bit?
Look here!
Jeez, at least give me an answer!
What do I do?
This won't do.
-One, two, three!
-Two, three!
Oh, no!
God, it's so cold!
-Chairman Kang!
-Why didn't you come out sooner?
Are you all right, Mr. Kang?
-What's this noise…
-It's so cold!
Chairman Kang!
Sir! How did you end up like this, sir?
-How did this happen?
-It's so cold.
This way.
This way, sir.
I might as well be
wearing shorts right now.
It's cold.
I'm sorry, sir.
Oh, my.
It's fine.
I'm so sorry, Chairman. Please forgive us.
There's no need for that.
Good luck with the rest of the shoot.
Well, then.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
-Take care.
-Yes, sir.
Goodbye, sir.
Take care.
Yes, sir!
I hope your new pants are comfortable!
I'm Associate Director Gye!
Ms. Shin, you should have been
more careful!
I'm sorry.
-Be careful yourself, Mr. Gye.
-What do you mean?
I think you're revealing
too much of yourself.
Before launching
"A Collaboration With the Chef,"
we are planning to put together videos
of interviews with the chefs
alongside the manufacturing process and
upload it to our social media platforms.
It's the researchers' shoot today, right?
Yes, sir.
We received a portion of the footage.
Would you like to take a look?
Sure.
Here are the premium ingredients…
That go food researchers
picked from the farm themselves…
To present to the chef!
Would you like to watch
some behind-the-scenes footage as well?
To present to the chef!
Cut! That was good. Let's do another take.
Ms. Shin, you don't need to keep
catching the cabbage.
I don't want it to fall and go bad.
A food researcher
should care about the ingredients.
We should use
this behind-the-scenes video.
Yes, I will, sir.
Come on, get it right!
Yes, sir.
Let's go again!
What?
Excuse me.
That's my mailbox.
Oh, hello. I live in unit 622.
I took your mail by mistake.
I'M SORRY
I TOOK YOUR MAIL BY MISTAKE
Sorry. If you're offended, I apologize.
No, it's okay.
It's human to make mistakes sometimes.
You apologized, so it's fine.
Because I'm cool like that.
Thank you for understanding.
-You moved here just recently, didn't you?
-Yes, how did you know?
Oh, I saw your furniture going in,
and you have a great taste in furniture.
You must like vintage products.
Oh, yes, well…
I'm actually a furniture designer,
so I couldn't help but take a peek.
You can tell a lot about a person
by looking at their furniture.
You're a designer?
After meeting like this,
let's not be strangers.
Sure. I can always say hi to my neighbors.
Look at that inconsiderate bastard.
Even with his grandfather in this state.
The hospital says you need to watch out
for just one thing.
What? What is it? What's wrong with me?
-The fact you're a hypochondriac.
-You little!
Even the CT scan says you're just fine.
Why are you being a crybaby?
I am not!
Do you know how hard I fell
because Shin Ha-ri, or Shin Na-ri,
or whatever her name is,
didn't bother to catch an old man
as he was falling over?
I'm sure Ms. Shin didn't do it on purpose.
I like her. She's good at her job.
Why would you like her?
Her hair was all messed up like this,
like she was a ghost or something.
That was a wig, right?
Anyway, I don't like her.
Is she shy?
But our Geum-hui is totally different,
isn't she?
She's around her age,
but look how bright and quick she is.
How nice is that?
Where should we send
the medicine that you requested, sir?
Oh, yes, about that…
What's Geum-hui's address?
What?
-Hello?
-Are you back from your business trip?
Oh, yes. I just got back home.
That's good. I'm in front of your house.
Can I see you for a moment?
You're in front of my house? Wait, why…
Where?
I have something for you.
It won't take long.
I'm so sorry, but I don't think
I can go out right now.
Really?
Then should I leave it at the shop?
At the shop?
No! Don't do that.
Did you wait long?
Who…
No. But what are you wearing?
This? I told my family
that I was going on a delivery.
In case they ask me
who I was going to meet.
I can't tell them
I'm meeting my fake boyfriend.
1. TELL ME WHAT YOU WANT
2. THERE ISN'T ANYONE
WHO RECOGNIZES ME, RIGHT?
3. MAN… THIS IS EMBARRASSING…
4. I'M IN SUCH A PICKLE…
Sorry, I didn't think that through.
I just wanted to give this to you.
What is this?
My grandpa went to a clinic
and ordered this special tonic.
Was he injured that badly?
What?
How did you know that he was injured?
GRANDPA, PAIN, CLINIC, TONIC
What? Well, I mean…
You said that he went to a clinic,
so I thought that maybe he got hurt?
He had a light fall,
but he tends to overreact.
Oh, okay.
Please tell him thank you for me.
And…
I picked up some ointment on the way here.
It's supposed to be good for bruises.
Use this.
Oh, you really didn't have to do this.
IS HE WORRIED ABOUT ME?
Thank you.
Oh, wait, I have something too!
Here.
Fried chicken?
I couldn't come out to deliver chicken
without bringing chicken, right?
Go eat it with your grandfather.
Our chicken is really good.
They're looking for me back at the store.
I'm going to go, then.
I'll see you this weekend.
Oh, my. Look at all this.
I thought he was just cold.
OINTMENT
But he has a sweet side to him too.
I went to see her face
to check if her bruise was okay.
What?
Why do I care if he's sweet or not?
Whatever.
Stop it!
Your eye looks completely healed now.
Oh, yeah. The ointment that you gave me
was really effective.
That's good to hear.
But where are we going right now?
It is our one-year anniversary after all,
so somewhere nice.
BE STRONG, GEUM-HUI
Are you stupid, Geum-hui?
Do you not have a mouth?
Why can't you just say
that I'm the man you love?
How can I say that
looking like this, Gwang-bok?
I want to buy all of this,
from here to here.
How much? How much do you need?
Hey, you have those clothes too, honey.
What do you mean?
Why would you display
clothes that are out of stock?
I'm right! The clothes that I bought you.
It's exactly what Geum-hui is wearing!
Anyway, that TV show makes no sense.
What kind of rich guy
buys his girlfriend a t-shirt
that's only 15,000 won?
That's all just advertisements.
They just film the show at any store
that's willing to sponsor them.
Young-seo said so.
Anyway, Geum-hui is so lucky.
Gwang-bok buys her
the entire store and everything.
I heard that Man-sik,
the guy who used to follow me around,
runs his own company now.
I'm sorry.
If only I had hidden
my love for you back then,
you wouldn't be living like this.
By the way, where did Ha-ri go again?
She's been going out every weekend.
-Maybe she's dating someone.
-Dating, my ass.
It's obvious.
She's probably with Young-seo,
chatting away and acting all pitiful.
-Welcome.
This way, please.
It smells really good.
Let's see this, this,
and everything from here to here.
Yes, sir.
What's with the cliché lines and vibe?
I think you've seen way too many TV shows.
Not me. It's my grandfather
who's seen too many.
What?
If we don't do this, he'll hear about it.
So do your best.
As if this is real, not fake.
Can you try on another one?
-We'll take a look at this one, too.
-Yes, sir.
How about this skirt?
I like this one.
What do you think, Geum-hui?
I like it too.
You have an excellent eye, sir.
Let me help you with your payment.
Do you have a bigger size?
I can't zip this up.
This is the only piece
in the country right now.
I'd say this fits very well, ma'am.
Really?
It's so damn expensive,
yet so damn stingy with the fabric.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Shall we go?
Hello. Long time, no see.
Oh, my god!
Ms. Jo! It's been so long
since we last saw you!
I need a dress to wear
to the Founding Anniversary Ceremony.
Then why don't you take your time--
Stop!
Never mind that.
Kim Se-jeong.
The dress that actress wore to
the press conference for her new show.
Only one of them has been imported
to South Korea.
Where is it?
I'm afraid it was just sold.
What? To who?
Over there…
Thank you.
That's Kang Tae-moo.
Who's the girl next to him?
Protect your skin
before time leaves a mark.
Cut! That was good.
Sir, let us touch up her hair and makeup
before the next shot.
Okay, let's do that.
Could you…
Could you touch up her hair
and blot some of the oil from her face?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Thanks.
Hello, my babies.
Okay.
Ms. Jin.
What are you doing?
-Aren't you going to greet your director?
-Oh, Director Jo, I'm sorry.
I didn't recognize you
because your face changes so much
every time I see you.
Did you touch up your forehead this time?
What do you mean?
I didn't "touch up" anything!
Don't you know that
I am a natural-born beauty?
Yu-jeong, if you're…
I mean, Director Jo,
if you're a natural-born beauty,
then is ramyeon an organic, superfood?
-Hey!
-What?
-Ma'am.
-Fine.
You seem to think you can act up
because of your dad.
But at work, I'm your boss.
I won't go easy on you
just because you're my cousin.
Then again, I'm sorry.
I'll be the bigger person.
You must be so stressed
because you were rejected by Kang Tae-moo.
Oh, my mistake.
What did you just say?
Kang Tae-moo.
Apparently, he has a girlfriend.
Her hair and eye makeup were stunning.
She was so much prettier than you.
I just saw them shopping at a boutique.
with my very own eyes.
Goodness, Director Jo!
Your employees are working
hard on the weekend
to shoot this commercial,
but you went shopping?
When you should be setting an example?
No.
No, that's not what I…
I just stopped by
to dress properly as a director.
For directors,
working hard is more important
than going shopping.
Also, if you have the time to go shopping,
maybe you should go to
the dermatologist too.
Look at all those wrinkles
around your eyes!
They look like noodles.
Hey! Where do you see any wrinkles
on my face, huh?
You should really go to the dermatologist.
It sounds like you're also
working hard today, Ms. Shin Geum-hui.
I'm sorry, Ha-ri.
That's a sample.
This is grilled sea bass
and anchovy salad.
It's been garnished with lotus root,
asparagus, and arugula puree. Enjoy.
It smells so good, doesn't it?
You must come here often.
The chef and the staff
all seem to recognize you.
You came with a girlfriend, right?
Would you take your boyfriend to
the chicken shop run by your own parents?
When they'd ask endless questions?
What are you talking about?
My grandfather owns this restaurant.
Chairman Kang Da-goo?
Well, the chef that you just saw
is the owner on paper.
This dish tastes quite familiar.
That dish was developed
at this restaurant, so I doubt it.
You know,
anchovies are fermented fish too.
Maybe it's because this is
pretty similar to jeotgal?
It tastes a bit like fresh kimchi!
You have a very accurate palate, Ms. Shin.
What?
Actually, I made this myself.
Really?
I've been planning
to make kimchi more localized.
In a country that doesn't have cabbage,
you could make kimchi with the most
popular vegetable of that country.
For example, making kimchi with cilantro
in Southeast Asia,
since that's popular there.
Or you could use anchovies
instead of fish sauce.
It's the same fishy taste,
but foreigners are more used
to the taste of anchovies.
I'm sorry. I'm boring you
with all this work talk, aren't I?
No, I'm enjoying it.
I'm always interested in food.
The food's going to get cold.
Let's eat.
Okay.
It sure is nice to have a gym
right in front of my place.
It's so big!
Let's get started then.
Hello.
Oh, right.
You said that you don't even
want to say hi to me, right?
I'll just cancel that "hello," then.
Just pretend it never happened.
You can use it first.
That's not what I wanted.
Oh, are you here to work out?
Oh, hello.
-All right, one second.
-Yes?
It's good,
but straighten your back a little bit.
Breathe out as you lower it.
Okay, let's raise it slowly now.
-Slowly?
-Yes.
He's handsome and has good manners.
And above all,
he's obviously interested in me.
But I'm just not feeling anything.
That one has no manners
and is super annoying,
and on top of that,
he has zero interest in me.
But look at that.
That's making me feel
a whole lot of different things.
He's totally my type.
You're a really good teacher.
No, I'm all right.
Hello.
Hey, what time is it?
I don't know. My phone's in my locker.
It's seven past eight.
Look over there.
Oh, thank you.
Why is someone who can see just fine
wearing glasses?
Here, take this.
What is it?
It's a standing lamp.
I wanted to apologize
for taking your mail last time.
No, it's okay. You didn't have to.
This is actually
something I designed myself.
You can just give me
some feedback in return,
so don't think too much of it.
You really didn't have to.
Thank you.
Why is this dress so tight?
I didn't even get to eat properly.
Crap, seriously?
Congratulations on
your one-year anniversary.
Thank you all for congratulating us.
Ms. Shin, shall we
blow out the candle together?
Sure.
One, two, three.
Come on, stop it. What's so funny?
Oh, sorry.
I've never seen clothes rip like that.
I told you, the issue is
with the clothes, not me.
How is this a small?
These are like kids' clothes.
The sizing of women's clothing is
problematic nowadays.
Great, now my heels are acting up?
Be careful.
Thank you.
I've never seen
the fireworks at Han River before.
I didn't realize when I watched it on TV,
but it's really pretty.
Isn't it?
Yes.
Very pretty.
Don't you have to tell your grandfather
about our date tonight?
Don't worry. Manager Oh probably
already told him all about it.
What do we do about this?
You can't even get a refund
because it's ripped.
It's a fake anniversary,
but it's still a gift.
Of course, I won't ask you to pay for it.
I had fun
on our fake anniversary date tonight.
I had fun too
on our anniversary date.
I better head inside.
I got to wear such expensive clothes.
Hey, Ha-ri! Hey, Shin Ha-ri!
Have you no conscience at all?
You were out all day
on this precious Saturday.
Can you switch with me now?
Okay, I'll be right out.
Get out.
The person you have called is unavailable.
Please leave your message…
Hey, Ha-ri.
Hey, Min-woo. What's up?
I brought some abalones for your mom.
-Really? Go ahead inside.
-Okay, see you inside.
Okay.
Why is Ms. Shin…
NATIONAL ID CARD
SHIN HA-RI
Hello?
Hello, Mr. Kang?
Shin Ha-ri, Shin Geum-hui,
Shin Ha-ri, Shin Geum-hui…
-Again.
Do you really not realize
who Shin Ha-ri is?
Schedule a meeting at two
with Food Product Development Team One.
You want me to go to
the Founding Anniversary Ceremony…
-Shin Ha-ri!
-Get this woman out of here, now!
Subtitle translation by: Su-in Choi
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs