BUSINESS PROPOSAL
EPISODE 3
Sorry.
-What are you doing here?
-Dad.
"Dad"?
-Running an errand for mom.
-Really? Let's go inside.
It's cold. Let's go in.
They're gone.
Mr. Kang. Get up, Mr.--
Come on. Mr. Kang!
Mr. Kang!
Mr. Kang.
This contract between "A" and "B"
aims to set the terms
of the simulated romantic relationship
between both parties
and the requested meetings
with the grandfather of "A".
In the case of a breach of contract,
the penalty shall be 100 times
the contract amount… 100 times?
But that's just ridiculous!
I was so dizzy
that I had to clear my entire schedule.
I lost an important contract.
Do you know how much that cost me?
Still, this isn't right!
Someone ordered a chicken from
your place, but you failed to deliver it.
-What would happen to its reputation?
-That's…
I'll just make it up--
There's no "next time" in this world.
You've lost trust.
You can't put a price on that.
But still, this isn't right.
Just accept my offer.
Then I won't sue for damages,
and I'll still pay you what I promised.
Mr. Cha? Contact legal and tell them
to proceed with the lawsuit right away.
No, I'll do it! Fine.
You're very impatient.
I've summarized
some things you need to know
to carry out this contract.
You need to memorize these things.
"Born in 1993, blood type B."
"Went to Hyunil private school
from elementary to high school."
"After graduating early, he was
admitted to Harvard at the age of 18."
At the age of 18?
BORN IN 1993
BLOOD TYPE B
"He graduated summa cum laude
from Harvard…"
"Thomas…"
How do you read that?
Thomas Hoopes Prize
for the Best Graduation Paper.
-What?
-It's a thing.
Oh, okay.
Wow, you were a track and field
athlete in college?
Wow, you got good grades and
were an athlete too? That's impressive.
My only flaw is that there's nothing
I'm not good at.
All the projects I've headed
at the company were all successful too.
A JOINT DEVELOPMENT OF THE
NEWEST FREEZER TECHNOLOGY
I see.
What's that?
"Fell in love while studying abroad
in New York."
-New York?
-Yes.
Since Mr. Kang has been in New York
for the past two years,
this backstory seems the most natural.
But I didn't study in New York.
To address that, we've put together
a backstory for you too.
DAD: TYPICAL LAWYER, MOM: TYPICAL DOCTOR,
HA-MIN: TYPICAL MED STUDENT
Typical?
This is a typical family?
Your family needs to seem
acceptable to Chairman Kang, so…
He'd faint if I told him
that my family runs a local chicken shop.
Anyway, the meeting with the chairman
is next Sunday.
Be sure to memorize the backstory
we've put together for you by then.
Okay.
I won't tolerate any mistakes,
do you understand?
SHIN GEUM-HUI
Shin Geum-hui,
you went to a really good school.
Why are you watching this?
Leave it.
Why can't you do anything by yourself?
I told you to leave it…
And if you're poor,
you should know your place in society.
The framework of this…
Graduated from Hyunil elementary, middle,
and high school. Went to Harvard, and…
TOP 20 GLOBAL LEADERS
SELECTED BY TIMES MAGAZINE
Geum-hui, you sure snagged yourself
a pretty impressive boyfriend.
-Geum-hui. Shin Geum-hui!
-Yeah?
Oh, Dad?
What are you daydreaming about?
Wow, you're getting really immersed
in your new identity, Ms. Shin Geum-hui.
Is this really worth all this effort?
What can I do?
Otherwise, I have to pay him
100 times the contract amount.
100 times?
100 times, my ass.
Did Ha-ri get spooked
by some absurd lie again?
He was going to press charges.
He would have found out my real name
and the fact that I work for his company.
Then what would happen? I'd get fired and…
Look, this is the best I can do.
So how's the studying coming along
on your fake boyfriend?
The more I learn,
the more unbelievable he seems.
Not only was he was born with
a diamond spoon in his mouth,
but he's also smart
and good at sports. Plus, he's hot.
But his parents passed away in
an accident when he was young.
Hey, I heard about that.
That's why there are no relatives
in any of the subsidiaries.
-Really? Why?
-Don't even get me started.
Rumor had it that someone was behind
the accident that killed his parents.
Really?
I mean, I have no idea
if that's the truth or not.
But apparently, Chairman Kang fired
all his blood relatives to protect him.
Yes!
What is it this time?
-Hello?
-Where are you right now?
Where else would I be at this hour?
Of course, I'm at home.
What is it?
I thought it would be best to discuss
this in a private space.
Oh, okay.
Did you memorize everything?
Yes.
Graduated from Hyunil schools.
Got into Harvard in 2010.
That's my grandson!
Joined go food after graduation.
After the success of Woorigo series
of bone broth, you were promoted quickly
and abruptly went to the New York
branch. As for your hobbies--
Enough!
What are you doing?
I heard that the chairman
was very thorough,
so I memorized
your entire profile just in case.
Do you think he'll ask you to recite it?
Still, I'm impressed, Ms. Shin.
You can't lose if you do it by the book.
Ask me anything. I'll get it right.
Is that so?
Then, if my grandfather asked to see you
on Saturday, two weeks from now,
what would be the correct way to respond?
Well, there's no real reason to say no
if your grandfather is asking to see me.
-So shouldn't I just say, sure?
-Wrong!
-"No" is the right answer.
-Why?
That day is our one-year anniversary.
Don't couples usually
spend time together on days like that?
-Are you sure you studied properly?
-But that was a trick question.
That's why simple memorization
won't always work.
Let me ask you something too, then.
What was I wearing when we first met?
-How could I possibly know that?
-Wrong!
Of course, you should remember!
After all, it was the first day we met.
On the day we first met,
it was raining in New York.
Just so you know, I looked up
the actual weather that day in New York.
That was as beautiful as the player I heard
at the Lincoln Center. Thank you.
I'm sorry.
No, it's fine. Are you all right?
Yeah.
His clothes look expensive.
What if he asks me
to pay for the dry cleaning?
Are you Korean?
Yes.
You too?
Falling in love just like that?
That's too unlikely.
Why? I think your grandfather
will be completely fooled
with the details
about the weather and everything.
I don't like rainy days.
Let's change the date instead.
You really don't have to drop me off.
It's late. Just accept the ride.
Yes, it wouldn't be right to let
a woman go home alone at this hour.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
We must be pretty close by now.
What? We still have a bit more to go.
I guess I was wrong,
That hurt.
I'll see you this weekend, then.
About Ms. Shin, isn't there something
oddly endearing about her?
Is being overly emotional
and easily distracted endearing?
Why are you smiling?
It's nothing.
Go on a blind date next week.
Are you pretending you don't know?
Or do you really not know?
Have you not heard
anything about my blind dates?
I've heard.
Yet you still want me to go on
blind dates?
That's why I looked internationally
instead of domestically.
Dad!
Do you want the rumors that I'm crazy
to reach international waters too?
I don't want to be set up with anyone!
You can't only do
the things you want to do.
As my heiress, you have responsibilities--
So you want me to have
an arranged marriage just like you?
You weren't happy,
and that's why you divorced.
Why do you want me
to go down the same path?
We…
-That was because your mom was eccentric.
-I'm just as eccentric as mom is.
I won't get married if I'm not in love.
So stop meddling in my life.
You insolent…
If you plan on acting however you please,
then move out!
Fine, I will.
I know you're famous for not
taking back anything you say.
So I'll do exactly as you ordered.
Hey, you…
Wait!
Wait.
I won't stop you from living on your own.
-But…
-But what?
-Leave my credit card behind.
-What?
Do you not know what it means
to be truly independent?
True independence is
living off the money you earn yourself.
What are you going to do
now that you have to eat your meals alone?
Taking away the credit card is
such a petty move.
In just three years, our dumplings now
make up the largest share
within the domestic market.
Furthermore, we are on the verge
of reaching a global sales revenue
of a trillion won, with the US
sales revenue being 400 billion won.
Let's have a round of applause!
Everyone, stop!
Our overseas market share
hasn't caught up with China's yet,
and you think it's time to clap?
I'm sorry, sir.
Have you set up a countermeasure?
Pardon? A countermeasure?
Well, that's…
I mean, a countermeasure--
If you're just going to read off
what your subordinates wrote for you,
you don't need to attend
these meetings from now on.
Now, let's move onto the next topic.
The Food Product Development Division's
"A Collaboration With the Chef".
Food Product Development Team 3…
will be under the direction
of Chef Jang Michelle.
-Michelle?
-That famous chef?
The super famous French chef?
How is Team 1 progressing on this?
Well…
We were developing an Italian family-style
meal with Chef Park Chun, but…
CHEF PARK CHUN'S BULLYING SCANDAL
ALL ACTIVITIES HALTED
This chef was just getting famous
but he turned out to be a bully?
I knew something was off about him
when he crushed garlic with his fists.
But then what about the dish
that we were working on?
Well, that's off the table now.
-How did it go?
-How do you think?
I got yelled at for not looking
into the chef's private life.
I told them that we would
look for another chef.
-Actually, I've already found a few.
-Yeah.
This chef is famous for his seafood.
CHEF HA JAE-WON
CHEF LEE JONG-JAE
This chef had a lot of TV exposure,
so he's already well-known.
But everyone in the industry
knows that we're looking
for a replacement for Chef Park.
Will it be okay?
Oh, Ms. Shin.
How about Chef Lee Min-woo?
-Min-woo?
-Yeah.
He's new, and his food is good.
Wouldn't he be a good fit?
Of course. That's why I recommended him.
Is he clean though?
He looks like a womanizer. What if
he causes a scandal after we hire him?
Don't bad-mouth an innocent guy
when you have no other alternatives.
I'm not bad-mouthing him.
He's just popular with girls.
Didn't you see him
completely reject Hye-ji?
You're right.
Judging by how he rejected me,
I don't think we'll have a problem.
Plus, he's super handsome,
and his food is great too!
I think we have a real shot at winning!
That's what I'm saying.
Get things ready so we can submit
a recommendation tomorrow.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Good.
You know, I even like
the name of your future wife.
Shin Geum-hui.
She has the same name as the
main character from my favorite TV show.
Let me hear it first.
Gwang-bok and Geum-hui
are finally together!
BE STRONG, GEUM-HUI
What kind of show makes the characters
get together after just one kiss?
This show is the worst.
Don't watch things like this.
Hey, what do you mean it's the worst?
Listen here, this show is hitting 27%
in viewership.
You just need to get into it.
Hey.
-Can you focus on the garnish?
-Okay.
-Wow, this is so good.
-Hey!
Have you been starving?
You should eat more slowly.
I haven't eaten all day because
I was looking for apartments at lunch.
Seriously, why did you move out?
Do you even have money
to get your own place?
You all seem to think that
I've been living off of my dad's money.
But I've saved up my paychecks.
Oh, sure. I'm sure you've saved a lot…
Min-woo, what about the
white kimchi ravioli?
I just called it ravioli,
but I made it with whatever I had at hand.
It's not even on the menu.
No. I think it'll make a perfect product.
A Korean-style ravioli.
-It's new.
-I don't know. Do you think it'll work?
Hey, don't you trust my taste buds?
I like your food for a reason, you know.
Go and make some, quick.
Okay.
"I like your food."
"And, I like you too."
I guess you don't want to
sleep over at my place tonight?
"I feel like sleeping out
on the streets tonight!"
-I'm sorry.
-Right?
Go eat.
What kind of security deposit
is this expensive?
This place doesn't even look like
it's half as big as my bedroom.
I thought you said you saved all your
paychecks without spending a cent.
So you were exaggerating.
On top of rent,
I also need to buy furniture,
and my living expenses
will be pretty high too.
Oh, that's right.
So I was thinking.
Should I just live with you?
In this room?
It was just a thought.
I'm going to get my own place!
You're a mean girl.
RECOMMENDATION
CHEF LEE MIN-WOO
It's so loud.
Turn off that alarm.
"Turn off the alarm"?
Get up. You're going to be late.
Ha-ri?
You fell asleep like this?
Your back will hurt.
Ha-ri, get up! Wake up!
Get up, you need to go to work.
What time is it?
What time do you think?
Oh, my God!
I haven't finished this! What do I do?
Get up and eat something first.
What? Food?
Right, I need to eat.
When did I fall asleep?
Wait, the recommendation…
Wait, I think I got to the part
about social media…
-Ms. Yeo.
-Yes?
I made the profile for Chef Lee
that you requested,
along with a proposal
for our collaboration.
Goodness, did you really finish
all of this in one day?
I had some ideas
from the last recommendation,
so it didn't take me very long.
White kimchi ravioli?
I wanted to cater to Korean taste buds
by using white kimchi for the filling.
Well, if it's dumplings,
then it can be mass-produced for sure.
What's this?
I thought President Kang
and other directors
might not know a lot about
Min-woo or his cooking,
so I compiled a list of reviews
for his dishes from social media.
THE RAVIOLI IS THE BEST!
IT'S QUITE GOOD, AND THE CHEF'S HANDSOME
Wow, he's really popular with women.
Yes. I think that will be an advantage
when we're marketing the products to
customers in their 20s and 30s.
But white kimchi ravioli?
Don't you think it's a bit risky?
I actually put some thought into that too.
We can just change the filling.
Like meat dumplings or kimchi dumplings.
The filling uses ricotta cheese as a base,
but there's an Italian version
using Italian sausages as well, and…
I can't. How am I supposed
to give a presentation to the president?
Why can't you?
You just need to do what you did
in front of me a moment ago.
It'd be better if you gave
the presentation, Ms. Yeo…
I've never had Chef Lee's ravioli,
and above all, I can't explain things
as well as you do.
-Let's go.
-Please, just wait.
She's right, Ms. Shin.
Director Go got yelled at so much
yesterday for making a mistake
while reading off of the papers that
a subordinate wrote for him.
Then you give the presentation, Mr. Gye.
Don't you know that Mr. Gye
has stage fright?
-You need to do it, Ms. Shin.
-One second.
I'm already feeling nervous.
This is a great opportunity
to get President Kang's attention.
It's because I shouldn't be
grabbing his attention right now.
Ms. Shin! Don't let me get embarrassed
in front of everyone and let's go!
Let's go!
Yeah, okay. Bye.
Wait!
A COLLABORATION WITH THE CHEF
CHEF RECOMMENDATIONS
Development Team 1,
is the chef list ready?
Actually…
Ms. Shin was supposed
to present for our team.
Why, is there a problem?
Well, that's…
I'm sorry for being late.
Hello, my name is Shin Ha-ri, from
Food Product Development Team 1.
The chef we're recommending--
You're going to present like this?
-Sir?
-Remove your mask. It's hard to hear you.
The mask…
What am I going to do?
I actually have a cold.
Just keep it on then.
Yes, sir.
The chef that we are recommending
is Chef Lee Min-woo of M Kitchen.
And the main menu is white kimchi ravioli.
The reason we are recommending this
chef is because of his genre of cooking…
Look, this place is in the middle of Seoul
and close to subway stations.
It's a great location.
So all these appliances come
with the apartment, right?
Of course, they come with the apartment!
There's a room too…
It's big.
In my 20 years working as a realtor,
I've never met anyone
as easy to please as you, miss.
I'm kind of like that.
Let's go down and write out the contract.
Sure.
The elevator's here.
Printing out the ingredient analysis
took so long that I'm late.
I need to hurry up and tell Min-woo!
Huh? I thought it was closing time.
Are there still customers?
Come on.
You can't just do that all of a sudden.
Look, I spilled this everywhere!
Ha-ri.
It's been a while, Ha-ri.
Yeah. It's good to see you, Yoo-ra.
You're here for work, right?
Oh, should I let you guys talk?
Oh, no, it's okay.
No, we can just talk later. It's fine.
-Bye.
-Wait…
Sorry. Were you shocked?
I was going to tell you before, but…
You've only had eyes on Yoo-ra
all this time.
But I still wanted to stay by your side
even just as a friend.
Because I thought that maybe you'd
look at me the same way one day.
That you might notice
how much I like you.
Yoo-ra wants to break up.
I really thought that.
That's my bus.
Sorry!
ARCHAEOPTERYX
Hello?
Ms. Shin.
Ms. Shin?
Oh, my.
Here you go.
ARCHAEOPTERYX
Thank you.
It must've hurt. Be careful.
It does hurt.
I thought it wouldn't,
but it hurts.
It hurts so much.
I wonder what happened.
Ninety-nine…
One hundred…
Nobody will be able to tell
that I was crying now, right?
All right.
Wig…
Oh, makeup.
A DAY TO SKETCH
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, HA-RI
FROM MIN-WOO
This show is today?
Why are you so spooked?
Mom says to come eat.
No, I need to go out.
I'm meeting someone today.
Hey! I like this group too.
This show is today.
If you're not going to go,
can I have this?
RECENT CALLS
ARCHAEOPTERYX
What?
I never talked to him yesterday.
What is this?
No way. Last night…
-Hi.
-Get in.
-You drove here yourself?
-This is a personal affair.
Did you call me yesterday?
I didn't know, but I saw
I had a call from you last night.
I'd called about today, but I hung up
because I couldn't hear anything. Why?
Nothing.
The weather is really nice today!
Maybe I should've taken
something to calm my nerves.
Are you nervous?
Didn't you say you've got this?
Mr. Cha said that your grandfather
is a really scary and strict person.
If he realizes that we're lying to him…
If you're scared, then while we're inside,
try to love me for real.
What?
Let's go.
Okay.
We're here.
Hey.
Ms. Shin Geum-hui!
You're as beautiful as I imagined.
Not her. Her.
What?
Oh, my.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, hello.
You said that you majored
in art in New York?
Oh, yes, sir.
I suppose that's why you seem so unique.
Since I was meeting the chairman,
I put on a lot of makeup so I wouldn't
get busted, but was it overkill?
Try this dish, sir.
They say potatoes are
good for hypertension.
Tae-moo told me about your hypertension.
I have diabetes, too.
Some bland vegetables like these
are probably better
than anything that's been cooked to be
all sweet and salty, right?
Ah, indeed. Eating habits are important,
but it's even better to combine it
with exercise.
I heard that you like hiking, right?
Yes, I do.
Do you like hiking as well, Ms. Shin?
Yes, I like it a lot!
Tae-moo, do you remember?
On Mount Brunni in Switzerland,
we enjoyed the stars together all night.
It was beautiful.
-Ms. Shin.
-Yes.
Do you love Tae-moo?
Of course!
I'm dating him because I love him.
Then why did you break up?
That's…
Grandfather. You can't just ask something
like that so directly--
I'm asking because it's something
that needs to be asked, you rascal.
Come on, answer me.
Well…
I thought that he cared about
work more than he did about me.
Tae-moo is someone who knows nothing
besides work.
That won't change in the future, either.
Are you okay with that?
Because you'll keep fighting about it.
Don't worry.
When we talked things over this time,
I decided I would understand that Tae-moo
prioritizes work over everything else.
He was so crazy about his work
that I ignored all his calls
after telling him "let's break up."
But he canceled an important meeting
he had scheduled and ran over to see me.
This boy
really skipped a meeting to go see you?
Yes.
On top of that, you know how
Tae-moo hates the rain, right?
It was raining that day,
and yet he still came.
Is that true, Tae-moo?
Let's eat first and discuss that later.
The food's getting cold.
What? Oh, right.
-Really?
-Yes.
The password is
written on top of the router.
Oh, okay. Thank you.
-Well, then.
-Thank you so much.
-Your sofa is here.
-Yes, I'm coming!
-Hello.
-Hello. The sofa's here! One moment.
Where should we put it?
I'm going to place it in the living room.
-Please be careful.
-Did you order Jajangmyeon?
Yes. Everyone seems
to have come all at once.
Could you wait with the food
for a moment so the sofa can go in first?
-Sure thing.
-Oh, the sofa, can go right here.
Okay.
It looks like someone finally
moved in next door.
-I have a package for you.
-Yes.
-Hello.
Thank you.
Could you please be
a bit more careful with the sofa?
I paid a lot of money for that.
-Package for you!
-Yes, please put it in front of the door.
Okay.
Careful.
-Oh, I need to pay, right?
-That will be 6,000 won.
Looks like my new neighbor's loud.
-Thanks.
-One second, I can--
-It's all right.
-Oh. Okay.
Enjoy your meal. It's fine.
I've been looking for you forever!
It was so awkward being with
your grandfather by myself, I was dying.
Hey, didn't I do well just now?
I don't think he liked me
very much at first,
but once I talked to him
about the rainy day,
he started getting into my story--
Why did you bring that up?
What do you mean?
That I ran to see you
on a rainy day.
You said that you don't like the rain.
So I added some truth to make
the story more realistic.
You ran to your lover
even though you hate the rain.
-How romantic is that?
-You must be mistaken.
But our relationship is
simply a contractual exchange of money.
Yes, right.
So don't act like
we're anything actually real.
Just answer his questions and don't
add any of your useless comments.
Got it?
Okay.
Ms. Shin.
Yes, sir.
Do you, by any chance,
like steamed buns?
Grandfather, today is--
I wasn't asking you.
Ms. Shin, do you like them?
Steamed buns…
Yes, I like steamed buns.
Then let's go eat
some steamed buns for dessert.
Let's take my car from here.
Damn steamed buns.
What did rain ever do to him?
Why is he being so touchy?
Wait for me, Tae-moo!
SUNRISE REALTOR
IBO CONVENIENCE STORE
Chairman Kang, hello!
Have you been well?
Of course, all thanks to you.
Let's go in.
After you.
We came all the way to Anheung
for steamed buns?
Don't complain.
You brought this on yourself.
Hey, what did I do that was so bad?
I just answered his questions
like you told me to.
What? Did I say something wrong?
I just did my best to do well…
-What are you suddenly doing?
-Your grandfather is watching.
Let's go, quickly.
Let's go, Tae-moo.
Here, eat.
Okay.
Let's see.
That's tasty.
They really are.
The bread is fermented really well.
The red bean filling is soft, too.
It was definitely worth the trip out here!
Hey, you got some red bean on your teeth.
My teeth? Oh, my!
What were the conditions?
Yes.
Have a drink.
Oh, yes, sir.
There we go.
Thank you.
That's it.
I apologize for today.
What do you mean?
For acting so stiff when I first saw you.
My first impression of the way
you were dressed wasn't the best.
I'm sorry.
It's all right, I understand.
I'm surprised
every time I look at myself, too.
Oh, and…
thank you.
Thanks for what?
Just for everything.
Anyway, it looks like Tae-moo
really cares about you, Ms. Shin.
Please keep taking good care of him.
Sure.
All right.
Oh, my.
-Are you all right, Ms. Shin?
-Oh, my. Yes. I'll pick those up.
-Oh, thank you.
-Here you go.
My goodness.
A DAY TO SKETCH
Let's go back to Seoul.
I have some business to take care of.
Business to take care of?
It's because you always act like that
that Ms. Shin can't even ask you
about things like this.
What did I…
-What are those?
-They're concert tickets.
Seeing as how they're for today,
she must have bought them to go with you.
Right, Ms. Shin?
-What?
-Get going right away!
Come on!
Here, take it!
Let's go, come on.
That little…
This is so nice.
I'm completely broke
after buying this sofa, though.
Should I have bought a cheaper one?
No.
This is a gift to myself to celebrate
my first time moving out on my own.
Good job, Young-seo.
It feels so good!
I'm so hungry.
Is moving always this hard?
Okay.
Is there a draft coming in from somewhere?
What?
Cockroach!
I hate cockroaches!
I hate them so much!
What's going on?
Sorry, there's a cockroach in my house.
You're…
Ms. Jin, what are you doing here…
Oh, well, it's a long story.
I'm sorry, but…
could I ask you for a favor?
It's inside that paper cup.
Right.
Sorry. I'm okay with everything else,
but I'm just really scared of bugs.
Sure.
Will it really die if you just
spray the outside like that?
I'm not sure. Don't you think it's dead
by now if I've sprayed this much?
Do you have another can?
Are you scared of bugs?
No, it's not that.
They just gross me out, that's all.
Isn't that the same thing?
-Oh, my God!
-That scared me.
I'm all right, but are you?
Yeah.
I'll finish it off. Get behind me.
He's using so much of the spray.
I flushed it down the toilet,
so there's no need to worry.
Thank you for helping me.
It was nothing.
Goodbye, then.
Wait.
Meeting like this as neighbors
is kind of fate,
so let's be friends
and get to know each other.
I'm sorry, but I don't think that'll work.
What do you…
You put Mr. Kang in a difficult position
by sending somebody else on the blind date
to fill in for you.
So I just don't think it would be right
for me to get to know you personally.
Wow.
Did I really just get rejected
as a neighbor too?
ART CENTER
I said we could go by ourselves but he
had to drop us off in front of the venue…
I know you too well.
It's so obvious you would pretend to go
then go back to work.
I want to watch the two of you
head inside.
Bye.
Let's go in then come back out
when your grandfather's gone.
Go ahead.
Goodbye.
He'll probably stay right in front
of the building until the concert starts.
Just give up.
You opened your eyes
As the light started to shine
You're like a gift that was prepared
Just for me
All of the small things
Just seem to get bigger
This moment
Where even my plain, everyday life
Becomes special too
A DAY TO SKETCH
We're the ballad duo, Melomance.
Thank you for coming.
Hello, everyone.
MELOMANCE IS OUR GIFT
OUR EVERYTHING, MELOMANCE
As a special event for our audience
members today,
we've taken song requests alongside
their special stories.
They do those things too!
"I've been a fan of yours
for a long time."
"I bought tickets for today's show and
gave them to a friend for her birthday."
"We've been good friends
for seven whole years."
"She even bought me drinks
and comforted me
when I broke up with my girlfriend
and when I had to go to the army."
"But she doesn't have a boyfriend yet."
"I'm hoping that she'll go to the concert
with her boyfriend."
"I ask that you gift her
with your amazing song."
Row B, seats 42 and 43! Are you here?
You came with a gentleman today!
-Oh, no, I…
-He's hot!
No…
I guess your friend's wish has come true!
I'm sure he'll be happy.
Congratulations to his friend
of seven years
for coming here today with a gentleman.
-Thank you.
-We'll sing "Love, Maybe,"
as requested.
My days are filled with daydreams
About all the things
That I want to do with you
When I see you happy
All I can do is smile
Everything you do makes my heart flutter
And I keep on spending
More nights wide awake
Thinking of all the little things you do
Do you know this song?
Sure. I really like this song.
Really? This one isn't that popular yet.
-Hey, sing it for me some time.
-What?
You're good at singing.
I was totally impressed
at the orientation.
Sure.
-This stop is Seoun University.
-Min-woo…
The next stop is Donggyo Arts High School.
I spend more and more days
Thinking of all the things
I want to do with you
This must be love
You'd get sick of me
If we spent all of our days together
Even when I turn around
You're all I can see
This must be love
Thank you, goodbye!
Watch where you're going.
Thanks.
I'll wash this and give it back to you.
Do you usually cry so easily?
You bawled yesterday too.
But you said you didn't hear--
It seemed like
you didn't want me to know, so…
Thank you for today. For everything.
For pretending you didn't notice
that I cried yesterday
and for coming to the concert with me,
which I would have gone to all by myself.
Not only that.
I almost looked like
a really pitiful person
because you cried like that
during the concert.
What are you talking about?
The women next to me were
talking about it pretty loudly.
That I was just your friend's replacement.
I'm sorry.
No need to be sorry.
I mean, it's not like
I'm your real boyfriend.
Did you really have a crush on him
for seven years?
Was it really that noticeable?
Isn't it obvious when you add up
your friend's message and your crying?
Anyway, I think you got
your closure today.
Yeah.
I'm going to accept that I got rejected
and end it, clean and simple.
That friend of mine got back together
with his ex-girlfriend.
I don't regret it, though.
I was really happy
for those seven years.
Someone like you who can't tolerate
wasting time can't understand that, right?
Well, it's not always that way.
What?
There are some things that get results
with a short amount of time,
and other things where you risk the
losses and stay in it for the long run.
It's difficult to decide how good or bad
something is just by how long it takes.
Why are you laughing?
There's nothing funny about that.
No, it's…
It's funny that you're comparing things
to your job even in a situation like this.
My apologies. I've never tried
to comfort anyone before.
That was comforting enough.
And I'm sorry about this afternoon.
I was feeling a little down so I overdid
things a bit so it wouldn't be so obvious.
I think that's why I said
some things I shouldn't have said.
No, I think I was being
a bit sensitive as well.
But where are we going right now?
I was just following you.
But I was following you.
THE BEST COMBINATION
TTEOKBOKKI, FRIED VEGGIES, SUNDAE
Can I have two tteokbokki, one sundae,
and a small fried veggie medley?
Do you want hard-boiled eggs?
No, I'm good.
Why? I can afford to buy us a snack.
Eat all you want.
No way!
You're not going to say a line
from a TV show where the rich guy says,
"I've never tried tteokbokki."
What do you take me for?
"Deliciously Spicy Tteokbokki"
is one of our products.
I came up with that.
I've been
to all the famous tteokbokki places
all around the country for that project.
-Here you go.
-That looks delicious.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Hey. I'm still outside.
Dinner?
I think I'm going to eat out.
Watch out!
Ms. Shin! Watch out!
Are you all right, Ms. Shin?
Ow, that hurts.
Put this on it.
Thank you.
Aren't you cold? Let me know if you are.
Mr. Kang.
Could I maybe make a small suggestion?
Sure. What is it?
Instead of a fake relationship like this,
why don't you try a real one?
You might think it's a waste of time
to be in a relationship right now,
but if you think long-term,
it might be more efficient.
You know, you could even get married.
-Married?
-Yes.
Being in a fake relationship with me
means there isn't really a future.
So maybe this is
an even bigger waste of time.
I think the taxi is here.
Well, then. I'm off.
Thank you again for today.
Get home safely.
I'll give you this in return.
I got it as a gift at the concert.
I don't know what it is,
but apparently, it'll cheer you up
when you're feeling down.
Bye!
Wow.
ARCHAEOPTERYX
Today was very inefficient,
but it was fun. Archaeopteryx.
TALK TO ME WHEN YOU'RE FEELING DOWN.
I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU.
Talk to me when you're feeling down.
I'll be there for you.
Be in a real relationship
instead of a fake one?
What do you guys think?
What am I doing?
-What is it?
-What? What's going on?
What happened?
I don't know. Maybe she threw a fit
while sleeping or something?
What am I going to do?
What's wrong with your face?
You scared me.
You think it looks bad too, right?
My goodness. I knew
the bruise would only get bigger.
Who plays catch on the streets at night?
You should've found out who they were
so I could teach them a lesson.
It's not like they did it on purpose.
It's okay.
-Look at this.
-Hey, Ha-ri, you look just like that.
Everybody was Kung Fu fighting
Do you want to die?
Okay, let's rub it a little bit, okay?
No, it's too late.
Just make me a fried egg with that.
-Okay.
-Just fry the egg.
Can you go to work looking like that?
I have to go.
It's not like I'm dying from this.
What are you doing? Give it to me.
-Get some gloves and finish cleaning.
-Get lost.
Wait, no way.
There's no way Mr. Kang would recognize me
by my bruise, right?
I almost didn't make it in time.
Will this be enough to cover the bruise?
-I realized
-It's President Kang!
that I don't know anything
about Shin Geum-hui.
She's that employee, right? Shin Ha-ri!
He looks a bit coldhearted…
Use this.
…but he has a considerate side too.
You and this supposedly fake relationship…
Have you fallen for him?
Subtitle translation by: Su-in Choi
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs